<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 17:53:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JWT Tokens in Express and NodeJS</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/jwt-tokens-in-express-and-nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 17:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/jwt-tokens-in-express-and-nodejs/</guid>
      <description>The JSON Web Token (JWT) is the easiest standard for protecting APIs and passing in claims data. A JSON Web token allows the server to verify the authenticity of the user and provide them access to protected API routes and data.&amp;nbsp; A simple JWT flow goes as follows:
 The user sends login credentials to the server The server verifies user against&amp;nbsp;the database then returns a JWT token if valid The user sends that token in the header with every request to API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a VPN Server</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/create-a-vpn-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 01:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/create-a-vpn-server/</guid>
      <description>There are three routes that you can take when setting up a VPN. You can either use a free one, buy a paid service or make your own. The advantage of free VPNs is that they are easy to setup; just install and they are ready to be used. My favorite VPN on Android is Opera VPN. The downside of Free VPNs is that they typically come with a 500 &amp;#8211; 1GB data cap and are very slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Phone From Android Wear</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-phone-from-android-wear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 14:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-phone-from-android-wear/</guid>
      <description>Security means everything to me. I am that guy who uses two step authentication on everything, along with safety backups and more. When it comes to security on Android, things aren&amp;#8217;t as tight as I would like them to be. On my S6, my favorite thing to use is the fingerprint scanner. I am aware that the fingerprint scanner does not offer better security than a strong password or lock pattern (although you could easily bypass the Android Lockscreen pattern), however, it will deter most people from trying to snoop around in my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>