<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>android wear on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/android-wear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in android wear on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 16:03:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/android-wear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Pokemon on Android Smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-pokemon-android-smartwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 16:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-pokemon-android-smartwatch/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever thought about playing Pokemon on your Android Wear Smartwatch? Neither have I. However, an app called Wear GBC makes this all possible. It is a Gameboy color emulator for Android Wear.
How to Play Pokemon on Android Smartwatch Here&amp;#8217;s a quick tutorial on how I got this up and running. First download a GBC ROM (.gbc). Then add it via the phone app (you might have to unzip it first if it&amp;#8217;s in a zip file).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Android Smartwatch 2016</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-android-smartwatch-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 15:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-android-smartwatch-2016/</guid>
      <description>I have been using the Huawei Watch for over two months now and I can safely say that it&amp;#8217;s the best Android smartwatch that I have ever owned. It features a high-quality aluminum design with a crisp 400 x 400 AMOLED display. There&amp;#8217;s even a speaker so that you can make phone calls and listen to music right from the watch. The only two things that I don&amp;#8217;t like about this watch is the weak vibration motor and the annoying pin charging mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Half Life on Android Wear</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-half-life-on-android-wear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-half-life-on-android-wear/</guid>
      <description>Just because you can, doesn&amp;#8217;t mean you should. But in this case, you totally should. If you recall, I demonstrated how to play Team Fortress Classic on Android using the SDLash app. The app is able to emulate the GoldSource game engine, which was used in many of the classic valve games such as Half-Life and Team Fortress. Right now, I am putting together a tutorial on how to play Half-life on Android, but in the meantime, check out how to do it on Android Wear (albeit a little more complicated).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Phone From Android Wear</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-phone-from-android-wear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 14:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-phone-from-android-wear/</guid>
      <description>Security means everything to me. I am that guy who uses two step authentication on everything, along with safety backups and more. When it comes to security on Android, things aren&amp;#8217;t as tight as I would like them to be. On my S6, my favorite thing to use is the fingerprint scanner. I am aware that the fingerprint scanner does not offer better security than a strong password or lock pattern (although you could easily bypass the Android Lockscreen pattern), however, it will deter most people from trying to snoop around in my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coolest Apps Android wear 2015</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/coolest-apps-android-wear-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 14:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/coolest-apps-android-wear-2015/</guid>
      <description>I love trying out new things with my smartwatch. Here is a video featuring the coolest Android wear apps 2015. If apps aren&amp;#8217;t your thing, no problem. Check out my video on the Top Android wear games for your device.
PixToCam  Video for Android Wear Wear Audio recorder Web Browser for Android wear Staylit Wear Have any other cool apps? Feel free to share below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows XP on Android Wear Smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/windows-xp-on-android-wear-smartwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/windows-xp-on-android-wear-smartwatch/</guid>
      <description>Alan Turing, the great father of computer science, had once said that, &amp;#8220;Machines take me by surprise with great frequency.&amp;#8221; I think we could all relate to that statement in one way or another. From the age of early gaming, to the development of PDA&amp;#8217;s, Smartphones, Smartwatches and even Smart Glasses, there never seems to be a point where technology fails to impress us. What is even more astonishing is how outdated technology can easily become to us within a small amount of time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>