<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Smartwatch on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/smartwatch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Smartwatch on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 16:03:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/smartwatch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Pokemon on Android Smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-pokemon-android-smartwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 16:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-pokemon-android-smartwatch/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever thought about playing Pokemon on your Android Wear Smartwatch? Neither have I. However, an app called Wear GBC makes this all possible. It is a Gameboy color emulator for Android Wear.
How to Play Pokemon on Android Smartwatch Here&amp;#8217;s a quick tutorial on how I got this up and running. First download a GBC ROM (.gbc). Then add it via the phone app (you might have to unzip it first if it&amp;#8217;s in a zip file).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Android Smartwatch 2016</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-android-smartwatch-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 15:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-android-smartwatch-2016/</guid>
      <description>I have been using the Huawei Watch for over two months now and I can safely say that it&amp;#8217;s the best Android smartwatch that I have ever owned. It features a high-quality aluminum design with a crisp 400 x 400 AMOLED display. There&amp;#8217;s even a speaker so that you can make phone calls and listen to music right from the watch. The only two things that I don&amp;#8217;t like about this watch is the weak vibration motor and the annoying pin charging mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar Watch</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/calendar-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 22:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/calendar-watch/</guid>
      <description>This is the Calendar Watch. It is a smartwatch by the company What? The Calendar Watch provides a unique take on smartwatches while adding in a good amount of luxury.
Enter in the Calendar Watch Giveaway Below: Calendar Watch Giveaway
**Open to anywhere that can physically receive packages from the U.S.**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coolest Apps Android wear 2015</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/coolest-apps-android-wear-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 14:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/coolest-apps-android-wear-2015/</guid>
      <description>I love trying out new things with my smartwatch. Here is a video featuring the coolest Android wear apps 2015. If apps aren&amp;#8217;t your thing, no problem. Check out my video on the Top Android wear games for your device.
PixToCam  Video for Android Wear Wear Audio recorder Web Browser for Android wear Staylit Wear Have any other cool apps? Feel free to share below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>