<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Device on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://bennettnotes.com/tags/device/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Device on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 15:50:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bennettnotes.com/tags/device/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LG G6 Unboxing</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/lg-g6-unboxing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 15:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/lg-g6-unboxing/</guid>
      <description>The LG G6 is a phone with little bezel and lots of curves. The rounded corners of the LG G6 look nice but definitely take some time to get used to. Is the LG G6 better than the Samsung Galaxy S8? Who will win the ultimate battle of LG G6 vs Samsung Galaxy S8? Only time will tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Note 7 Exploding</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/galaxy-note-7-exploding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 14:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/galaxy-note-7-exploding/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube XdylvXX2G0g {}
Samsung has recalled Galaxy Note 7 devices world wide due to incidents of explosion. What causes these devices and other Lithium-ion batteries to malfunction?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LG G4 Quick Review</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-quick-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 02:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-quick-review/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube ysvFJYHgSoE {}
tl;dr
The LG G4 is seriously one of the best Android smartphones of 2015. It might not have the most attractive design on the outside and in the UI, but it is very responsive and can last you through a whole day with moderate-heavy usage.
The LG G4 Quick Review: Here is a quick review of the LG G4.
Screen: The LG G4 has a 2560x1440p display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LG G4 Gaming Performance</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-gaming-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 15:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-gaming-performance/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube o5Ka-wVYTxo {}
LG G4 Gaming Performance: Here is a quick look at the LG G4 gaming performance. If you are worried with LG&amp;#8217;s decision to use the Snapdragon 808 over the Snapdragon 810, don&amp;#8217;t be. In my testing, I used graphics heavy games such as GTA Vice City and Goat Simulator along with Real Racing 3. I could not get the device to lag, even with all the in game settings set to the max.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Root Any Android Device</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-root-any-android-device-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-root-any-android-device-2014/</guid>
      <description>There are some things in life that sound too good to be true. However, this isn&amp;#8217;t one of them. George Hortz, a hacker made famous by his iOS jailbreaks and PlayStation hacks has managed to root the Verizon Galaxy S5. So why should you care? Well, he used a recently discovered exploit found in all Linux kernels that were built prior to June 3rd. So in theory (and in practice) his app should work on any Android device that has a kernel build date prior to June 3rd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build Custom Cyanogenmod Rom</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-custom-cyanogenmod-rom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 08:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-custom-cyanogenmod-rom/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube GAyxypK7_K8 {}
Build Custom Cyanogenmod Rom? So are you ready to take on Rom Development? That&amp;#8217;s okay if you&amp;#8217;re not, because I&amp;#8217;ll help walk you through it. In this tutorial, I&amp;#8217;m going to show you how to build your own Cyanogenmod Rom right from source. This sounds a lot more complicated than it actually is though. However, keep in mind that you will need a lot of patience when doing this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>