<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux Chromebook on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/linux-chromebook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux Chromebook on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 13:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/linux-chromebook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Run any OS on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-os-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-os-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>If Chrome OS is not fulfilling your needs, all hope isn&amp;#8217;t lost. You can run any OS on a Chromebook as long as it has an x86 processor (Chromebooks with an Intel Processor). That means you can run Windows on your Chromebook or even run Mint Linux on your Chromebook.
You will need to have developer mode enabled on your Chromebook  Run Any OS on Chromebook In order to run any OS on your Chromebook, you will have to enable the legacy bios with USB booting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Kali Linux on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-kali-linux-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-kali-linux-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Kali Linux is a popular security focused operating system. It offers a lot of&amp;#8230;eh&amp;#8230;&amp;#8221;interesting&amp;#8221; use case scenarios. To install Kali Linux on the Chromebook is very easy. Crouton (the popular open source script that is used to install other operating systems on the Chromebook such as Ubuntu on Chromebook) can be used to install Kali Linux on Chromebook.
Before you begin! You will need to have developer mode enabled on your Chromebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Linux on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-linux-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 13:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-linux-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Tired of Chrome OS? Do you want to play games like Minecraft or Steam Games on your Chromebook? Luckily, Linux allows you to accomplish some of that. To install Linux on Chromebook, we are going to use the crouton script. The script takes care of all of the downloading and configuration. All you need to do is run a couple of commands.
You need to make sure that you have developer mode enabled on your chromebook before attempting this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>