<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wifi on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/wifi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wifi on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 15:59:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/wifi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Android as Microphone</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/use-android-as-microphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 15:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/use-android-as-microphone/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever needed a microphone, but did not have one available? Have you ever searched for a way to make a cheap wireless microphone? Needless to say, you can use your Android device as a microphone. There are two ways that this can be accomplished. The first is through traditional cables, and the second is through additional software. If you want to use your Android device as a microphone through USB, Wifi or Bluetooth, then skip to the second method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/reverse-tether/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 13:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/reverse-tether/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever been stuck in a situation that you needed WiFi but only had an Ethernet connection available? Unless you&amp;#8217;re looking to connect your phone to an Ethernet connection, you would be all out of options. I found myself in a similar situation when I needed to setup a live stream using a bunch of laptops and only one Ethernet connection with no WiFi available. This is also useful if you are looking to avoid using mobile data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disable Lock screen at Home</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/disable-lock-screen-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 15:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/disable-lock-screen-at-home/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s face it, at home, there might not be a huge risk to leaving your phone unlocked. Yes, a sibling could snoop into your phone and take a look at those risque pictures you have saved or see who you have been texting, but that might not be the absolute worst security breach to deal with. Luckily, Android Lollipop adds a trusted device feature that allows you to automatically disable your lock screen if you are on a trusted wifi network or connected to a trusted Bluetooth device.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>