<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Computer on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/computer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Computer on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 03:31:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/computer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheapest Computer You Can Buy</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/cheapest-computer-can-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 03:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/cheapest-computer-can-buy/</guid>
      <description>If you are in the market for a computer that will cost you about the same price as a large Starbucks iced coffee, then you are at the right place. Introducing, the Raspberry Pi Zero W. The Raspberry Pu Zero W is the cheapest computer you can buy. This computer isn&amp;#8217;t made for gaming or bitcoin mining. It&amp;#8217;s aimed at developers and enthusiasts to use in their projects. It would also make for a great setup for a small home server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/reverse-tether/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 13:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/reverse-tether/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever been stuck in a situation that you needed WiFi but only had an Ethernet connection available? Unless you&amp;#8217;re looking to connect your phone to an Ethernet connection, you would be all out of options. I found myself in a similar situation when I needed to setup a live stream using a bunch of laptops and only one Ethernet connection with no WiFi available. This is also useful if you are looking to avoid using mobile data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read Car Computer with Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/read-car-computer-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 15:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/read-car-computer-android/</guid>
      <description>You can use a bluetooth OBD II tool with your Android device to read important information from your car&amp;#8217;s computer and even see real time data.
OBD II: https://goo.gl/rQb68v
Torque App: https://goo.gl/UDNCDT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer on Fire!</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/computer-fire-giveaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 15:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/computer-fire-giveaway/</guid>
      <description>My Computer Caught on Fire! Oh&amp;#8230;and here&amp;#8217;s a giveaway too.
Giveaway is now closed! Thanks to all who entered!
You can also purchase the 8000Mah ToughTested case here:
http://goo.gl/d4WlSH</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remotely Turn on Computer with Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/remotely-turn-on-computer-with-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 22:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/remotely-turn-on-computer-with-linux/</guid>
      <description>I really wish more people used WOL. It is probably one of the most underrated things in the world of wired networking. If you aren&amp;#8217;t familiar, WOL (Wake on Lan) allows you to remotely turn on your computer. This could be from another computer or even your Android device. It works by supplying a little bit of power to your Ethernet card to allow it to listen for the &amp;#8220;wake up&amp;#8221; signal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a Supercomputer</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-a-supercomputer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 03:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-a-supercomputer/</guid>
      <description>So you want to build a supercomputer? Well, if you checked out my video on quantum computing you&amp;#8217;ll know that scientist are working to make computers stronger and faster than ever. Unfortunately, building a quantum computer is not something you can do at home, unless your home is a laboratory of course. All hope isn&amp;#8217;t lost though, you can still go on to build your very own supercomputer. To do this, we will be making a Linux cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Computer from Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-computer-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 16:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-computer-android/</guid>
      <description>Consider this, you are sitting across the room chilling on your couch and you&amp;#8217;re starting to fall asleep. Here&amp;#8217;s the problem, your couch feels so good and you don&amp;#8217;t want to get up to lock your computer, but you need to because you have nosy roommates. So wouldn&amp;#8217;t it be great if you could remotely lock it from your phone? Okay, so even if this situation is completely unbelievable, this is still something cool to try and do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boot Computer from Android Phone</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/boot-computer-from-android-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 02:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/boot-computer-from-android-phone/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself in a situation where you didn&amp;#8217;t have a flash drive handy? Well, the other day I was trying to re-install Windows on my laptop, and sure enough, my USB flash drive conveniently went missing. Luckily, I was able to use my Nexus 5 to mount the ISO and boot my laptop from it. So here&amp;#8217;s how you can boot computer from Android phone:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/share-computer-internet-connection-with-android-reverse-tethering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 23:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/share-computer-internet-connection-with-android-reverse-tethering/</guid>
      <description>Everyone is familiar with tethering. However, many people overlook the ability to reverse tether. Reverse tethering allows you to share your computer&amp;#8217;s internet connection with your phone or tablet. This is useful if you&amp;#8217;re on a metered data plan or in an area which has no wifi and a weak mobile signal. 
What You Will Need:  A rooted Android Device A Windows PC USB Driver Reverse Tether Zip (Go to this thread to download or direct download here)  Step 1: Install USB Drivers If you don&amp;#8217;t have any device drivers already installed on your computer and you never used adb before, then you will need to install the USB drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>