<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>happiness on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/happiness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in happiness on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 10:08:42 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/happiness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Only Live for the Weekend</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/why-i-live-for-the-weekends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 10:08:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/why-i-live-for-the-weekends/</guid>
      <description>Everyone tells me, &amp;ldquo;Dave, you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be living just for the weekend!&amp;rdquo; But I wonder, how do people who work in a typical 9-5 corporate environment avoid lusting over the liberty and excitement that the weekend brings. Two whole days to do what you want to do; spending time with family or friends, traveling, working on side projects, gaming, etc. For me, it means two whole days where I don&amp;rsquo;t have to be in a windowless room coding in front of a computer screen for eight hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s bad about coding? You can work for hours with nothing to show for it</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/something-to-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 05:51:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/something-to-show/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday, I spent several hours working on my website&amp;rsquo;s code. I added some new meta tags to lazy load images, tried to remove JQuery dependencies from my scripts, added enhancements for accessibility and structured data, and even created a pull request for the theme that I am using (Beautiful Hugo).
Basically, five hours of my day were eaten up by completing those tasks. Although this was another example of getting too absorbed in your side projects, I was actually proud of myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness and Anticipation</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/happiness-and-anticipation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 12:46:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/happiness-and-anticipation/</guid>
      <description>I am beginning to see the relationship between happiness, anticipation and dopamine.
Dopamine is a neurotransmitter that is responsible for reward-driven behavior and pleasure seeking. (Psychology Today). When we get a hit of dopamine, we feel good!
Anticipation is the simple act of looking forward; usually to a pleasurable experience but it could also be negative.
In my previous post about Proven Ways to be Happy Again, I mentioned this thing called hedonic adaptation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientifically Proven Ways to Be Happy Again</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/scientifically-proven-ways-to-be-happy-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 06:02:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/scientifically-proven-ways-to-be-happy-again/</guid>
      <description>During the winter holidays (peek depression season), I took a free online course called The Science of Well-Being offered by Yale University. It was actually recommended in a HackerNews comment that I came across in a thread about different MOOC (Massive Online Open Courses) to take.
Other than my obsession with self help porn, I took this course because I wanted to learn on how to be happy again with life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>