<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 06:03:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I want to do everything so I do nothing</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/i-want-to-do-everything-so-i-do-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 06:03:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/i-want-to-do-everything-so-i-do-nothing/</guid>
      <description>One of the most challenging areas of self discipline in life is time management. I often find myself in situations where I do not have enough time to complete all the things that I want to do. And it&amp;rsquo;s not because I am procrastinating; the second I get home from work I jump right into some new side project or video. The problem is that there are simply too many things that I want to do right now, and learning the personal discipline to say no to myself is challenging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complacency After College</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/complacency-after-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 06:00:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/complacency-after-college/</guid>
      <description>Up until graduation day, everything made sense. I&amp;rsquo;ll go to class, get good grades, then land a decent paying job so that I can move out of my parents and &amp;ldquo;start my life&amp;rdquo;. Amazingly, all of that happened fresh out of college at 22 years old. Back then, a couple of my peers have told me, &amp;ldquo;Damn dude, you&amp;rsquo;re living the dream.&amp;rdquo; In reality, I felt like I was far from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Too Absorbed in Your Side Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/getting-too-absorbed-into-your-side-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 07:01:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/getting-too-absorbed-into-your-side-projects/</guid>
      <description>When I start working on a side project, I fall into a really bad habit of getting too absorbed in it. The second I get home from work, I will start coding and testing for hours until I have to force myself to go to bed with only six hours of sleep at best. All the while, my laundry starts to pile up, my kitchen doesn&amp;rsquo;t get cleaned, and my social contacts get neglected from any meaningful conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Switched From WordPress to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/why-i-switched-from-wordpress-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 06:04:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/why-i-switched-from-wordpress-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>WordPress isn&amp;rsquo;t awful. In fact, I recommend WordPress to everyone who wants to start a blog. Despite this, I switched from WordPress to Hugo a couple of weeks ago. The real reason came down to cost and simplicity.
Cost Running a WordPress blog meant that I needed a good shared hosting environment with a MySQL server and PHP execution. I first tried Hostgator, and it was sufficient enough while my blog had less than a hundred of visitors per month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness and Anticipation</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/happiness-and-anticipation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 12:46:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/happiness-and-anticipation/</guid>
      <description>I am beginning to see the relationship between happiness, anticipation and dopamine.
Dopamine is a neurotransmitter that is responsible for reward-driven behavior and pleasure seeking. (Psychology Today). When we get a hit of dopamine, we feel good!
Anticipation is the simple act of looking forward; usually to a pleasurable experience but it could also be negative.
In my previous post about Proven Ways to be Happy Again, I mentioned this thing called hedonic adaptation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>