<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gaming on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/gaming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gaming on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 02:52:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Steam Games to Android 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-android-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 02:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-android-2017/</guid>
      <description>If all Android phones came with DirectX and desktop graphics, then playing native games would be a breeze. Unfortautnetly, that is far from the case. So while you might not be able to play Fallout 4 on android, there is nothing stopping you from streaming it to your device. Here&amp;#8217;s how you can Stream Steams Games to Android.
What You Will Need:  Nvidia 600 series or better graphics Card GeForce Experience App Moonlight  If your graphics card doesn&amp;#8217;t fit the requirements, then check out my other tutorial on how to Stream Steam Games to Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Pokemon on Android Smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-pokemon-android-smartwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 16:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-pokemon-android-smartwatch/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever thought about playing Pokemon on your Android Wear Smartwatch? Neither have I. However, an app called Wear GBC makes this all possible. It is a Gameboy color emulator for Android Wear.
How to Play Pokemon on Android Smartwatch Here&amp;#8217;s a quick tutorial on how I got this up and running. First download a GBC ROM (.gbc). Then add it via the phone app (you might have to unzip it first if it&amp;#8217;s in a zip file).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counter Strike on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/counter-strike-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/counter-strike-android/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
How would you like to play one of the most popular PC games of all time on your Android device? So, maybe playing Half-Life 2 and Team-Fortress classic on Android isn&amp;#8217;t cool enough for you. Well, how about Counter Strike on Android? Of course, this isn&amp;#8217;t going to be the latest Counter Strike Global Offensive with the Source Engine. It&amp;#8217;s going to be the old school original counter strike from the late 90s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Steam Games to Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-to-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 13:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-to-android/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to play Team Fortress or PlanetSide 2 on your Android device? Well, there is no way to do that, unless you&amp;#8217;re looking to play Team Fortress Classic on your Android device. However, you could stream these games from your computer to your Android device.
Currently, the most popular method used to stream games to Android is some combination of limelight and Nvidia&amp;#8217;s Game Stream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Play PS2 Games on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-ps2-games-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 03:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-ps2-games-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>I always said to never underestimate the power of Chromebooks, and here is another reason not to. You can play play PlayStation 2 Games on your Chromebook. In order to do this, you will need to have Linux** installed on your Chromebook. **We are going to use the popular PCSX2 emulator for Linux. So it&amp;#8217;s also important that you have an Intel powered chromebook.
Now, one word of advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LG G4 Gaming Performance</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-gaming-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 15:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-gaming-performance/</guid>
      <description>LG G4 Gaming Performance: Here is a quick look at the LG G4 gaming performance. If you are worried with LG&amp;#8217;s decision to use the Snapdragon 808 over the Snapdragon 810, don&amp;#8217;t be. In my testing, I used graphics heavy games such as GTA Vice City and Goat Simulator along with Real Racing 3. I could not get the device to lag, even with all the in game settings set to the max.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play PSP Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-psp-games-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 19:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-psp-games-android/</guid>
      <description>Play PSP Games on Android Yes, you can play PSP games on your Android device. This is not a gimmick, nor some sort of absurd remote VNC. This is pure emulation right on your Android device. It is all thanks to the app PPSSPP. Surprisingly, some games work with excellent frame rate and graphics quality (Naruto for example). Keep in mind though, not every game will be compatible and it will not work with every device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable Ultra High Graphics Dead Trigger 2</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/enable-ultra-high-graphics-dead-trigger-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/enable-ultra-high-graphics-dead-trigger-2/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s not surprising that certain games purposefully limit the maximum graphics level that the user could set. However, it becomes an issue when the device you&amp;#8217;re playing on is more than capable of handling the maximum graphics level, even though the developers didn&amp;#8217;t think so. Unfortunately, Dead Trigger 2 is a perfect example of this scenario. Fortunately, with a little file modification you can enable the secret &amp;#8220;ultra&amp;#8221; graphics mode only accessible to latest generation iPhones and Tegra devices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>