<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mods on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/mods/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mods on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 13:49:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/mods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Theme any App</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/dark-theme-any-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 13:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/dark-theme-any-app/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love dark themes in my apps. Not only is it easier on the eyes, but having a true amoled black theme could save you battery life on certain devices like the Galaxy S8. Unfortunately, not every app comes with a dark theme option. So if you want to dark theme any app on your device you will need to use the theme engine called Substratum. Substratum could give you a dark theme Instagram, dark them Facebook, dark theme Inbox, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallout 4 Tweaks</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/fallout-4-tweaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 16:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/fallout-4-tweaks/</guid>
      <description>Fallout 4 has been one of my favorite games of the year, but it isn&amp;#8217;t perfect. Everyone is aware how&amp;#8230;lacking&amp;#8230; Bethesda can be with their games. However, thanks to the modding community, many of the issues that you might encounter in Fallout 4 can be fixed.
One of the biggest complaints about Fallout 4 has been the FPS lock and not supporting 21:9 widescreen monitors. If you&amp;#8217;re feeling adventurous, you can dig through the game&amp;#8217;s ini file and adjust the values accordingly, but the easier solution would be to download the Fallout 4 Configuration tool which allows to you use a simple GUI that will make Fallout 4 tweaks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>