<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chrome on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/chrome/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chrome on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 06:58:38 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/chrome/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix: Could not establish connection. Receiving end does not exist</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/fix-receiving-end-does-not-exist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 06:58:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/fix-receiving-end-does-not-exist/</guid>
      <description>If you are developing a Chrome extension with message passing, then you might have received the following error: Unchecked runtime.lastError: Could not establish connection. Receiving end does not exist.. There was some type of behavior change that happened post Chrome 72 that affected the way channels are opened. Essentially, if you try to call runetime.connect() before you have a a channel open, then you will get this error (Stackoverflow).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a Chrome Extension</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-a-chrome-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 15:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-a-chrome-extension/</guid>
      <description>Chrome extensions are really cool. They allow the user to extend the capabilities of their browser and can incorporate really well into existing apps. So let&amp;#8217;s take a look at how to build a Chrome Extension in less than 10 minutes. Chrome Extensions are written in Javascript, so I recommend that you have a basic understanding of Javascript before proceeding with this tutorial.
What we&amp;#8217;re building We are going to build a simple chrome extension that will allow you to search google for any text that you highlight on a page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Read USB</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-read-usb-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 17:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-read-usb-2/</guid>
      <description>You can now officially use JavaScript to read USB devices that are connected to your computer. This is using the new WebUSB API that is still in early draft. As being so, the API could later change or be removed altogether until it receives the final verification.
In order to use WebUSB you need to be running the latest version of Google Chrome, with the experimental web platform features flag enabled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Extensions for Google Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-extensions-google-chrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-extensions-google-chrome/</guid>
      <description>The best thing about Google Chrome is all the extensions that are available for it. Now I recently learned that Microsoft Edge also has extensions, but nowhere near as many as google chrome. By no means is this an exhaustive list of all the best extensions for Google Chrome; just a few of my favorites that I use every day.
Ghostery 
If you are concerned about your privacy on the internet, then Ghostery is the perfect app for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Cortana use Google</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/make-cortana-use-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 04:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/make-cortana-use-google/</guid>
      <description>As you know, Microsoft Cortana has become an integral part of Windows 10. I wouldn&amp;#8217;t mind Cortana so much if Microsoft didn&amp;#8217;t force it upon us. One thing which really bothers me about Cortana is that it defaults to Microsoft Edge and Bing. I am a Google person, so I would prefer if it used Google Search and Google Chrome. Before the Windows 10 Anniversary update, there used to be a way to change the default behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hearthstone on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/hearthstone-on-chromebook-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 20:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/hearthstone-on-chromebook-2/</guid>
      <description>Hearthstone is a very popular game which I coincidentally don&amp;#8217;t play. However, I do spend quite a lot of time on my Chromebook and love seeing how far I can push its compatibility with software. Naturally, the idea of running Hearthstone on Chromebook appealed to me. After all, Counter Strike, TeamFortress and PlayStation 2 games work, so I don&amp;#8217;t see why Hearthstone wouldn&amp;#8217;t.
If you haven&amp;#8217;t guessed already, we are going to be using Linux to make this work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hearthstone on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/hearthstone-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 20:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/hearthstone-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Hearthstone is a very popular game which I coincidentally don&amp;#8217;t play. However, I do spend quite a lot of time on my Chromebook and love seeing how far I can push its compatibility with software. Naturally, the idea of running Hearthstone on Chromebook appealed to me. After all, Counter Strike, TeamFortress and PlayStation 2 games work, so I don&amp;#8217;t see why Hearthstone wouldn&amp;#8217;t.
If you haven&amp;#8217;t guessed already, we are going to be using Linux to make this work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/mac-os-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 19:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/mac-os-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Do you ever come across some crazy ideas? Well, this is certainly one of them. Running Mac OS on Chromebook is a lot easier than you think. Now keep in mind, you aren&amp;#8217;t going to be able to do anything intensive on this. This is more a proof concept (like a lot of things that I do) and something just to admire.
To do this, we are going to be doing some very convoluted emulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Kodi on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-kodi-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 04:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-kodi-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Kodi (formely Xbmc) has become a popular in-home media platform. Luckily, getting it on your Chromebook is not much of a challenge. However, you will need to make sure that you have Linux installed on your Chromebook first. Here&amp;#8217;s a short video on how to install Kodi on Chromebook.
Terminal commands:
sudo apt-get install software-properties-common sudo add-apt-repository ppa:team-xbmc/ppa sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install kodi </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Steam Games Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 15:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Hopefully it is clear by now that Chromebooks are not meant for gaming of any type. However, that hasn&amp;#8217;t stopped many of you from accomplishing things like playing CS:GO on your Chromebook or PS2 Games. However, games like CS:GO and TF2 will work on almost any piece of hardware, but something like Fallout 4 won&amp;#8217;t.
If you&amp;#8217;re still determined to game from your Chromebook, you can do so via streaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Chrome OS on PC</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-chrome-os-on-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 02:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-chrome-os-on-pc/</guid>
      <description>I recently came to the realization that Chrome OS is in some ways a perfect operating system. No, I swear I&amp;#8217;m not taking any hallucinogens. Here is a scenario that really opened my mind. I have an aunt who uses a basic low spec PC running Windows XP. All she does is check her email and check Facebook once per day, and that&amp;#8217;s it. Unfortunately, her PC barely meets the requirements to run Windows XP effectively and is constantly cluttered from maleware, Trojans, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Minecraft Server on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-minecraft-server-on-chomebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 18:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-minecraft-server-on-chomebook/</guid>
      <description>So do you have a Chromebook sitting around that you have absolutely no idea what to do with? Well, if you or your buddies are minecraft junkies, then why not consider turning your Chromebook into a Minecraft server. It runs slightly faster than using your Android phone as a minecraft server, and offers a playable speed(though it can lag occasionally).
Now before you do this, you need to make sure that you have Ubuntu Installed on your Chromebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counter Strike Global Offensive on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/counter-strike-global-offensive-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 15:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/counter-strike-global-offensive-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Counter Strike Global Offensive on Chromebook? Are you tired of playing the same old games on your Chromebook? Well, with a little help from Linux and Steam you can play CS:Go on your Chromebook. Of course, this will only work with the Intel powered Chromebooks. As far as performance, it&amp;#8217;s playable. On average, I am getting around 23-30 fps in games. It&amp;#8217;s nowhere close to the performance that I get on my desktop, but is still playable none the less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Android apps on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-android-apps-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 22:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-android-apps-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Recently, Google has released an Android run-time for Chrome OS that will allow developers to easily port their android applications to Chrome OS (Feel free to watch the Keynote for more information). While this is a step in the right direction (and should have been included with Chrome OS from the very beginning, but I digress) there are only four official android apps available for Chrome OS (Evernote, Vine, Sight Words, Duolingo).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Android on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-android-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 05:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-android-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of Chrome OS? Do you want a greater selection of apps and games? Well, running Android on your Chromebook is a practical option. The performance is without compromise and almost everything works (except for the touchpad). You will have access to the entire Google Play store so you can download games and thousands of apps. So here&amp;#8217;s how to run Android on Chromebook.
What You Will Need:  An Intel Powered Chromebook A USB with at least 2GB of free space Android X86 iSO Rufus  Step 1: Developer Mode Before you can run Android, you will need to put your Chromebook in developer mode.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>