<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 05:46:53 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying a Drone With Javascript</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/flying-a-drone-with-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 05:46:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/flying-a-drone-with-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Flying a drone with javascript probably sounds crazy and hard. Do I use a framework? Will the 10 GB of node_modules weigh it down? NOPE! It&amp;rsquo;s all pretty simple to do.
The other day I came across a neat drone called the DJI Tello. It is a relatively inexpensive quadcopter that offers a simple SDK which can be accessed over WiFI. Using the NodeJS dgram library, I can send commands via UDP to the drone to perform actions such as takeoff, left 20, and land.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success from Things You Don&#39;t Care About</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/what-you-want-vs-what-sells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 05:57:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/what-you-want-vs-what-sells/</guid>
      <description>I had just finished a YouTube that I spent a week working on; a couple of days working on the graphics, a day of voice recording, and a few more hours coming up with a nice thumbnail. I uploaded it, and eagerly awaited the YouTube algorithm to award my quality work with a burst of views and watch time. I sat and waited in anticipation. Hour one went by, nothing. Okay, maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just a little slow today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s Monthly Keyword Search Volume Doesn&#39;t Matter</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/seo-search-volume-does-not-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 05:53:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/seo-search-volume-does-not-matter/</guid>
      <description>I spent the last month focusing a lot on seo (Search Engine optimization). One of the biggest mistakes that I made was using Google&amp;rsquo;s monthly keyword search volume as an indicator on whether a particular keyword has sufficient search volume to pursue. Google&amp;rsquo;s monthly keyword search volume is completely wrong. I found large discrepancies when comparing my actual data from Google analytics to what Google says the traffic should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Declutter and Clear Your Mind</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/learning-to-declutter-and-clear-your-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 06:06:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/learning-to-declutter-and-clear-your-mind/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a mental hoarder. If you were to look inside my head, you would find all types of mental clutter. Boxes labeled &amp;ldquo;random shower thoughts&amp;rdquo;, trashcans full of personal bullshit, and a closet overflowing with reminders, ideas and useless information. This creates a negative impact on my ability to recall and recollect. I often find myself in this awkward situation where this was something I know I took a mental note of, but I just can&amp;rsquo;t remember what it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Want to Do Everything so I Do Nothing</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/i-want-to-do-everything-so-i-do-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 06:03:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/i-want-to-do-everything-so-i-do-nothing/</guid>
      <description>One of the most challenging areas of self discipline in life is time management. I often find myself in situations where I do not have enough time to complete all the things that I want to do. And it&amp;rsquo;s not because I am procrastinating; the second I get home from work I jump right into some new side project or video. The problem is that there are simply too many things that I want to do right now, and learning the personal discipline to say no to myself is challenging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrape Google Search Using Puppeteer</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/scrape-google-search-using-puppeteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 05:50:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/scrape-google-search-using-puppeteer/</guid>
      <description>For my side project, I needed to scrape Google search using a headless browser. I ended up using the Nodejs library called puppeteer. It&amp;rsquo;s a headless browser that uses chromium.
Install puppeteer npm install puppeteer Scrape Google Search using Puppeteer First, let&amp;rsquo;s go to the google homepage, type something in, and click the search button.
try { (async () =&amp;gt; { const browser = await puppeteer.launch(); const page = await browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complacency After College</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/complacency-after-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 06:00:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/complacency-after-college/</guid>
      <description>Up until graduation day, everything made sense. I&amp;rsquo;ll go to class, get good grades, then land a decent paying job so that I can move out of my parents and &amp;ldquo;start my life&amp;rdquo;. Amazingly, all of that happened fresh out of college at 22 years old. Back then, a couple of my peers have told me, &amp;ldquo;Damn dude, you&amp;rsquo;re living the dream.&amp;rdquo; In reality, I felt like I was far from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Hyperledger Fabric on Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/install-hyperledger-fabric-on-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 17:09:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/install-hyperledger-fabric-on-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>I recently had the &amp;ldquo;amazing 🙄&amp;rdquo; opportunity to spend two weeks figuring out how to install hyperledger fabric on Kubernetes. There aren&amp;rsquo;t many guides on the internet besides this one. Unfortunately, I found it to be very vague and missing some keys steps.
For this tutorial, let&amp;rsquo;s go step-by-step on how to install hyperledger on kubernetes. We are going to use some information from the guide linked above, along with some stuff my team and I were able to figure out along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Too Absorbed in Your Side Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/getting-too-absorbed-into-your-side-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 07:01:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/getting-too-absorbed-into-your-side-projects/</guid>
      <description>When I start working on a side project, I fall into a really bad habit of getting too absorbed in it. The second I get home from work, I will start coding and testing for hours until I have to force myself to go to bed with only six hours of sleep at best. All the while, my laundry starts to pile up, my kitchen doesn&amp;rsquo;t get cleaned, and my social contacts get neglected from any meaningful conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Switched From WordPress to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/why-i-switched-from-wordpress-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 06:04:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/why-i-switched-from-wordpress-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>WordPress isn&amp;rsquo;t awful. In fact, I recommend WordPress to everyone who wants to start a blog. Despite this, I switched from WordPress to Hugo a couple of weeks ago. The real reason came down to cost and simplicity.
Cost Running a WordPress blog meant that I needed a good shared hosting environment with a MySQL server and PHP execution. I first tried Hostgator, and it was sufficient enough while my blog had less than a hundred of visitors per month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness and Anticipation</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/happiness-and-anticipation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 12:46:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/happiness-and-anticipation/</guid>
      <description>I am beginning to see the relationship between happiness, anticipation and dopamine.
Dopamine is a neurotransmitter that is responsible for reward-driven behavior and pleasure seeking. (Psychology Today). When we get a hit of dopamine, we feel good!
Anticipation is the simple act of looking forward; usually to a pleasurable experience but it could also be negative.
In my previous post about Proven Ways to be Happy Again, I mentioned this thing called hedonic adaptation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientifically Proven Ways to Be Happy Again</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/scientifically-proven-ways-to-be-happy-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 06:02:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/scientifically-proven-ways-to-be-happy-again/</guid>
      <description>During the winter holidays (peek depression season), I took a free online course called The Science of Well-Being offered by Yale University. It was actually recommended in a HackerNews comment that I came across in a thread about different MOOC (Massive Online Open Courses) to take.
Other than my obsession with self help porn, I took this course because I wanted to learn on how to be happy again with life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read System Environment Variables in Angular</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/angular-read-system-environment-variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 07:14:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/angular-read-system-environment-variables/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks back I was working on a project where I needed to read system environment in Angular 7 from a Docker container before it builds. After days of searching, I came across a solution from multiple sources on the internet.
Keep one thing in mind, you will only be able to inject environment variables before your Angular app builds. Unlike Nodejs, you will not get real time access because you are running in an browser environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Setup Search on Hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/how-to-setup-search-on-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 06:11:06 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/how-to-setup-search-on-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Setting up search on your static site built using Hugo or Jekyll is not as difficult as it sounds. If your static site is hosted on GitHub pages (which mine currently is), then you will not be able to use php or any server side scripting. Therefore, we must rely on a pure javascript solution.
Using Lunr.js Lunr is a popular library used to parse through data and return the most accurate match based on a search query.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ebooks are not social</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/ebooks-are-not-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 18:26:46 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/ebooks-are-not-social/</guid>
      <description>If you are trying to be more social, consider investing in traditional books over EBooks. I know this sounds crazy, and no, Amazon did not pay me to say this.
Ebooks are missing an important aspect that we have always took for granted in traditional book. There is no easily visible cover! This means people have no idea on what you&amp;rsquo;re reading. With traditional books, its out in the open for everyone to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to download any video from any site for free</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-download-any-video-from-any-site-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 02:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-download-any-video-from-any-site-for-free/</guid>
      <description>You have probably discovered that downloading videos from certain websites is hard. If you try to download a video from youtube, you have to use one of the ad-infested free YouTube video downloaders. Other sites like Facebook, Instagram and Tumblr are even harder to find downloaders for. Luckily, there is a free and open-source program that will end your struggles and help you download and video from any site for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove Bloatware from Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-remove-bloatware-from-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 15:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-remove-bloatware-from-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>Believe it or not, Windows 10 comes with a lot of bloatware pre-installed on it. Things like Candy crash, Bing Weather, Bing Sports, etc. If you really wanted to, you could go through the programs and features tool and remove each app individually. However, that would take a lot of unnecessary time and some apps wouldn&amp;#8217;t show up in that menu. To overcome this challenge, a user on GitHub created a Windows 10 bloatware removal script that uses PowerShell to remove the unnecessary apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel 3 Review – Don’t Romanticize Imperfection</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/pixel-3-review-dont-romanticize-imperfection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 16:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/pixel-3-review-dont-romanticize-imperfection/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s not romanticize imperfection. The Pixel 3 is not _The Little Engine That Could, _or some gifted boy who was born without legs. There are people out there who treat Google like the underdog; despite the fact that they have full control over the future of Android. And while there&amp;#8217;s nothing wrong with having favorites in a race, it can be dangerous to idolize a runner just based off his shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Share WiFi Connection on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-share-wifi-connection-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 14:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-share-wifi-connection-on-android/</guid>
      <description>Last summer, I was staying at a beautiful resort in the Dominican Republic with no access to mobile data, so I needed to depend on WiFi. Unfortunately, my network access only allowed me to have one device at a time on the network. This was a huge pain because I wanted to connect both my phone and laptop to the network. After some searching, I found out a simple way to share wifi from an android device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Control Android from Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-control-android-from-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 12:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-control-android-from-android/</guid>
      <description>There is an easy way that you can control one Android device from another Android device. This is useful if you need to perform any type of tech support for someone else&amp;#8217;s device. To control Android from Android we can use the free app TeamViewer Quick Support.
Compatibility: This is not compatible with every Android device. TeamViewer has a full list of the supported manufacturers. Unfortunately, if you have a Google Pixel device then you will not be able to take advantage of the remote control capabilities; you will only be able to share your screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best windows 10 Screensavers 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-windows-10-screensavers-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-windows-10-screensavers-2018/</guid>
      <description>Here is a collection of some of the best Windows 10 screensavers that you should try.
Fliqlo Fliqlo is my favorite Windows 10 screensaver of 2018. It has such a clean and minimalistic look that goes great with the design of my room.
Sun Village This is a screensaver from Nvidia. It&amp;#8217;s a nicely rendered 3D scene with lots of activity happening. It looks bright and vibrant and you can even enable the built-in FPS counter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Computer Science Degree Was Not Worth the Cost</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/my-computer-science-degree-was-not-worth-the-cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 13:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/my-computer-science-degree-was-not-worth-the-cost/</guid>
      <description>I am a 2018 college graduate with a bachelor&amp;#8217;s degree in computer science. I recently got hired for my first full-time software developer job. As any new graduate, I was eager to go to work and put this shiny new degree to good use. After just a few weeks on the job, I had a horrible realization. Four years of undergrad and \$80K taught me nothing of value for today&amp;#8217;s job market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Block All Ads on Android without ROOT</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-block-all-ads-on-android-without-root-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-block-all-ads-on-android-without-root-2/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;#8217;t think that I have ever encountered anyone who said that they like ads (other than maybe the Super Bowl ads). Nonetheless, ads are a necessary evil which must be tolerated in order to compensate for various internet endeavors. However, there are many apps, games, and websites which abuse ads and destroy the entire experience. In the past, blocking ads from these apps required that you root your device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Block All Ads on Android without ROOT</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-block-all-ads-on-android-without-root/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-block-all-ads-on-android-without-root/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;#8217;t think that I have ever encountered anyone who said that they like ads (other than maybe the Super Bowl ads). Nonetheless, ads are a necessary evil which must be tolerated in order to compensate for various internet endeavors. However, there are many apps, games, and websites which abuse ads and destroy the entire experience. In the past, blocking ads from these apps required that you root your device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to theme and customize Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-theme-and-customize-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 10:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-theme-and-customize-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>Windows 10 doesn&amp;#8217;t have many cool options when it comes to theming. Fortunately, there are developers out there who went the extra step to create theme patchers and ither awesome skins. In this tutorial, I want to show you how you can get your Windows 10 desktop looking like the image below.
Dark Theme The dark theme I used is called After Dark CC. Although it&amp;#8217;s a paid theme ($2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Games to Chromebook using Moonlight</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-games-to-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 13:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-games-to-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>If you want to play Fortnite or PUBG on a Chromebook, you can do this through streaming. It&amp;#8217;s very easy to stream games to Chromebook using Moonlight. The only requirement is that you need to have an NVidia 600 Series or higher graphics card.
Enable Streaming in GeForce Experience App The first thing you need to do is enable streaming in the GeForce Experience app.
Install Moonlight Extension on Chromebook You can go here to download the moonlight extension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Enable Ultimate Performance Mode in Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-enable-ultimate-performance-mode-in-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 13:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-enable-ultimate-performance-mode-in-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>The Windows 10 April update brought a lot of new features. One of the little-known features is a new power plan called ultimate performance mode. According to Microsoft, this mode decreases the micro-latency between the OS and the hardware. Exactly what that means, I&amp;#8217;m not too sure. However, this mode is more than just made up fluff.
I ran a couple of benchmarks between using the default balanced mode on my PC and the ultimate performance mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JWT Tokens in Express and NodeJS</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/jwt-tokens-in-express-and-nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 17:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/jwt-tokens-in-express-and-nodejs/</guid>
      <description>The JSON Web Token (JWT) is the easiest standard for protecting APIs and passing in claims data. A JSON Web token allows the server to verify the authenticity of the user and provide them access to protected API routes and data.&amp;nbsp; A simple JWT flow goes as follows:
 The user sends login credentials to the server The server verifies user against&amp;nbsp;the database then returns a JWT token if valid The user sends that token in the header with every request to API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React Login with Google Firebase</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/react-login-with-google-firebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/react-login-with-google-firebase/</guid>
      <description>There are many opinionated solutions for building a React Login with Google Firebase. I generally prefer an approach where the user isn&amp;#8217;t shown the main UI until he is logged in. And if the user logs out, we immediately kick him back to the login screen. Luckily, this isn&amp;#8217;t hard to do at all.
Dependencies The only dependency you will need is the Firebase API. You can install this form the Node Package Manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a Chrome Extension</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-a-chrome-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 15:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-a-chrome-extension/</guid>
      <description>Chrome extensions are really cool. They allow the user to extend the capabilities of their browser and can incorporate really well into existing apps. So let&amp;#8217;s take a look at how to build a Chrome Extension in less than 10 minutes. Chrome Extensions are written in Javascript, so I recommend that you have a basic understanding of Javascript before proceeding with this tutorial.
What we&amp;#8217;re building We are going to build a simple chrome extension that will allow you to search google for any text that you highlight on a page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain and Decentralization will NOT fix the Internet</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/blockchain-and-decentralization-will-not-fix-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/blockchain-and-decentralization-will-not-fix-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>Stop saying that blockchain and decentralizing everything will fix the Internet. There has been a lot of news around Cambridge Analytica abusing Facebook profile data, and Facebook for mining user data without explicit permission. Yes, I agree that these are very bad things that need to be addressed. And I also agree that while Facebook is at the front-lines of this digital privacy war, we could also blame many other companies like Google, Twitter, Amazon, etc for similar practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React Native StackNavigator Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/react-native-stacknavigator-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 02:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/react-native-stacknavigator-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>I have spent hours trying to figure out how to actually use the React Native Stacknavigator to navigate between screens. All the tutorials and guides seem to be missing important information, and the official React Native documentation is truly lacking in substance. So I want to save you some headache and give you a quick and easy setup to using the React Native StackNavigator.
You need to Eject If you created your react-native project using the command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Poly API Javascript and NodeJS</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/google-poly-api-javascript-and-nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 01:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/google-poly-api-javascript-and-nodejs/</guid>
      <description>Google has been working on an interesting project called Poly. With Poly, you have access to hundreds of 3D objects that can be used to build VR games or with AR content. The interesting about Poly is that all of the graphics are available on demand. Think of it like Google Fonts just for 3D objects. So let&amp;#8217;s take a look at how you can get started with Google Poly API Javascript and NodeJS bundle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React Context API</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/react-context-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 03:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/react-context-api/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m sure you have probably heard of the fancy new React Context API. It&amp;#8217;s a new way for you to manage application state. If you are building a large react application, you have probably encountered a problem where you needed to access and share data across multiple components. For example, we might have information on the currently authenticated user that multiple components need information on. To solve this issue, you might use a library like Redux or Mobx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React Native Android App Receive Data from Share Intent</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/react-native-android-receive-data-from-share-intent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 01:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/react-native-android-receive-data-from-share-intent/</guid>
      <description>This whole problem started when I was working with an app in React Native. I wanted the app to be able to open when it received data from another app through the &amp;#8220;share with&amp;#8221; intent. For example, if I share an URL through the YouTube app, I wanted my app to be recognized as one of the apps that could handle the URL and open it.
I am going to spoil the fun and tell you that there&amp;#8217;s no easy way to do it straight through javascript with React Native.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typescript Getter and Setter</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/typescript-getter-setter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 00:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/typescript-getter-setter/</guid>
      <description>This is something that you probably don&amp;#8217;t ever think about, but getters and setters are implicit on every javascript object. For example, if we take the following:
person = {}; person.name = &#39;Dave&#39; //uses the implicit setter on the object console.log(person.name) //uses the implicit getter The above code is something that you have probably have seen very often in javascript. However, this doesn&amp;#8217;t give you much control over how properties are accessed or defined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angular 4 input only numbers Directive</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/angular-4-input-numbers-directive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 00:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/angular-4-input-numbers-directive/</guid>
      <description>I was working on a project in Angular 4 and needed to implement input fields that only accept numerical values. My first thought was to simply add the HTML5 type=&amp;#8221;number&amp;#8221; to the input. Unfortunately, this isn&amp;#8217;t supported in Internet Explorer 10 and some of the clients would most likely be using Internet Explorer 10. My only other option was to implement a directive. Thanks to this StackOverflow answer, I was able to modify it to my needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Token Interceptor and Retry in Angular 4</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/implementing-token-interceptor-and-retry-in-angular-4-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 14:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/implementing-token-interceptor-and-retry-in-angular-4-2/</guid>
      <description>If you are building a web application using Angular 4 or Angular 5 there&amp;#8217;s a good chance that you might be working with JWT tokens. Luckily, implementing token interceptor and retry in Angular 4 and beyond is very easy thanks to the new HTTP Interceptors. Using this, we can add an authorization header to every outbound request while also implementing a retry mechanism for requests that fail due to an expired token.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Token Interceptor and Retry in Angular 4</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/implementing-token-interceptor-and-retry-in-angular-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 14:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/implementing-token-interceptor-and-retry-in-angular-4/</guid>
      <description>If you are building a web application using Angular 4 or Angular 5 there&amp;#8217;s a good chance that you might be working with JWT tokens. Luckily, implementing token interceptor and retry in Angular 4 and beyond is very easy thanks to the new HTTP Interceptors. Using this, we can add an authorization header to every outbound request while also implementing a retry mechanism for requests that fail due to an expired token.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple CSS Hack Can Steal Internet Passwords</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/simple-css-hack-can-steal-internet-passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 16:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/simple-css-hack-can-steal-internet-passwords/</guid>
      <description>A user on GitHub just posted an alarming exploit shows how a simple CSS hack can steal internet passwords. It&amp;#8217;s kinda funny how you wouldn&amp;#8217;t really think of CSS when it comes to vulnerabilities and hacking. Since CSS is only used to style a webpage, its threat level is generally considered to be relatively low.
However, CSS does provide developers with very advanced selectors. In this case, if you wanted to select an input with the value of A in it and turn it red, then CSS allows you to do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a forum</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-a-forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 14:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-a-forum/</guid>
      <description>Practically every online community has a forum. It makes sense though because forums are a great way to facilitate online discussion. Now let&amp;#8217;s say that you wanted to build your own online forum. Well, building a very basic forum wouldn&amp;#8217;t be too complicated. Just script together some PHP with an MYSQL database and you will be all set. Unfortunately, this would likely leave you vulnerable to many potential security holes and a terrible user experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Windows Applications (EXE Files) on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-windows-applications-exe-files-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 01:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-windows-applications-exe-files-on-android/</guid>
      <description>If I had a dollar for the number of times someone asked how to run Windows Exe Files on Android, I would be richer than your top Bitcoin miners. Most of the time, my response would have simply been that it&amp;#8217;s not possible, end of story. Well, that sort of changed this week.
If you are a Linux user, you have probably heard of Wine. The tl;dr is that Wine allows you to run Windows apps in Linux (it&amp;#8217;s a Windows compatibility layer).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angular 4 Forms</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/angular-4-forms-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 15:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/angular-4-forms-2/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite features in Angular are forms. Using Angular 4 forms or Angular 5 forms are very helpful because they provide for quick validation and object mapping. Here&amp;#8217;s how you can create a basic angular 4 form (also works with angular 2, and angular 5).
HTML You will also notice that I am using Bootstrap for some styling, that is completely optional. Let&amp;#8217;s look at the form HTML:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angular 4 Forms</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/angular-4-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 15:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/angular-4-forms/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite features in Angular are forms. Using Angular 4 forms or Angular 5 forms are very helpful because they provide for quick validation and object mapping. Here&amp;#8217;s how you can create a basic angular 4 form (also works with angular 2, and angular 5).
HTML You will also notice that I am using Bootstrap for some styling, that is completely optional. Let&amp;#8217;s look at the form HTML:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Recyclerview for Installed Apps with Checkbox</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-recyclerview-for-installed-apps-with-checkbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 15:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-recyclerview-for-installed-apps-with-checkbox/</guid>
      <description>One of the most common reasons that you would want to use the android recyclerview is if you want to show a list of some sort. In this example, let&amp;#8217;s take a look at how you can use the android recyclerview to show a list of installed apps on your device. Within each item, we will also include a checkbox. Here&amp;#8217;s what it will look like:
Layout Let&amp;#8217;s first take care of creating the layout files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Machine Learning to Predict the Value of Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/use-machine-learning-to-predict-the-value-of-bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 22:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/use-machine-learning-to-predict-the-value-of-bitcoin/</guid>
      <description>The day has finally come at which I can use machine learning and bitcoin in the same article. The only thing that would impress me more would be relating the topics of machine learning, bitcoin, and blockchain in the same article, but I digress. Anway, the value of bitcoin is astonishing. It went from $900 to well over $14,000 in less than 6 months time! So hey, let&amp;#8217;s start riding this bubble and try to cash in before its too late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meltdown and Spectre – Possible Javascript Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/meltdown-and-spectre-javascript-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 15:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/meltdown-and-spectre-javascript-vulnerabilities/</guid>
      <description>This has been a very interesting New Year. So far, 2018 has brought us two of the biggest bugs to hit CPUs in the past 12 years: Meltdown and Spectre. Intel is struggling to get their Meltdown bug under control while Amazon and Microsoft brutally await its impact on their cloud services. Both Meltdown and Spectre are serious issues, but Meltdown is easier to exploit and gives attackers more valuable information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Chrome Extensions for Web Development</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-chrome-extensions-for-web-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 03:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-chrome-extensions-for-web-development/</guid>
      <description>Google Chrome and its developer tools are an absolute necessity for any web developer. But you shouldn&amp;#8217;t stop there because there are even more great tools and extensions that will help you with web development and design. So let&amp;#8217;s take a look at some of the best Chrome extensions for web development.
React Developer Tools If you plan on doing development in React, then you should definitely download this extension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap Navbar Collapse in ReactJS</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/bootstrap-navbar-collapse-reactjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 15:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/bootstrap-navbar-collapse-reactjs/</guid>
      <description>Bootstrap is an amazing library and works wonders with ReactJS. Unfortunately, you can&amp;#8217;t (or really shouldn&amp;#8217;t) use Bootstrap.js with React because bootstrap directly manipulates the DOM; which could break React&amp;#8217;s nice rendering flow. This becomes a big problem if you wanted to implement a Navbar using plain bootstrap. Take the following for example from Bootstrap&amp;#8217;s documentation:
&amp;nbsp;
You could directly take this code and put it in ReactJS (but change class _to _className) and you will have a working Navbar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP Query SQL Database return JSON</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/php-query-sql-database-return-json/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 15:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/php-query-sql-database-return-json/</guid>
      <description>As a Javascript developer, I always prefer to use NodeJS as my API endpoint when interacting with a backend database. Unfortunately, it&amp;#8217;s not always feasible to use NodeJS (especially in a shared hosting environment) and you might have to fall back to good old PHP. So here&amp;#8217;s a quick refresher on how you can perform queries to a SQL database using PHP from an Ajax or Fetch call.
Fetch Call Suppose I have the following XMLhttp request using the fetch API:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP insert into SQL database from Fetch POST</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/php-insert-sql-database-fetch-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 15:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/php-insert-sql-database-fetch-post/</guid>
      <description>As a Javascript developer, I always prefer to use NodeJS as my API endpoint when interacting with a backend database. Unfortunately, it&amp;#8217;s not always feasible to use NodeJS (especially in a shared hosting environment) and you might have to fall back to good old PHP. So here&amp;#8217;s a quick refresher on how you can insert an object into an SQL database from javascript using php. If you haven&amp;#8217;t already, check out my previous tutorial on making SQL queries from PHP using fetch API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPU Programming in Javascript</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/gpu-programming-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/gpu-programming-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>You probably don&amp;#8217;t think about Javascript when you hear the words GPU programming. However, it should come as no surprise that there is a library to do anything and that includes GPU Programming in Javascript. Let&amp;#8217;s get one thing clear though, you should probably not do this if you are looking to do serious GPU programming. For serious GPU programming, I recommended that you work with Nvidia&amp;#8217;s CUDA in C and C++.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Classification using Nvidia Digits – Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/image-classification-using-nvidia-digits-deep-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/image-classification-using-nvidia-digits-deep-learning/</guid>
      <description>Nvidia digits is a great way to get started with deep learning and image classification. It&amp;#8217;s an open source platform that you can run on your computer to do things like image classification, object detection, and processing. It also contains a REST API so that you can easily do all of this through HTTP requests if you desire. For this tutorial, let&amp;#8217;s take a look at image classification using Nvidia digits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Linux on Surface Laptop</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-linux-on-surface-laptop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 15:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-linux-on-surface-laptop/</guid>
      <description>It might be crazy to run Linux on Surface Laptop, but there is a way to do it. If you have extra RAM to spare on your Surface Laptop, just use Virtual Box because you&amp;#8217;ll have all the driver support you need and you will not have to change your boot configuration. For the brave, here&amp;#8217;s how to install Linux on Surface Laptop the more traditional way.
Be Careful! Once we change the boot configuration on your Surface Laptop, you will need to enter your recovery key to unlock your hard drive (which is locked by BitLocker by default).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Javascript for of vs for in vs for each</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-vs-vs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 14:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-vs-vs/</guid>
      <description>If you are new to Javascript (or even a seasoned js developer), you will probably get confused when trying to understand the different types of for loops. So let&amp;#8217;s go through the javascript for of vs for in vs for each loop.
Standard for loop Suppose we have an array called myArray. Here&amp;#8217;s how you would iterate through it using the standard for loop:
var myArray = [&#39;Cat&#39;,&#39;Dog&#39;,&#39;Horse&#39;]; for(let i =0; i&amp;lt; myArray.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subscribe to variable change in Angular 4 Service</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/subscribe-to-variable-change-in-angular-4-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/subscribe-to-variable-change-in-angular-4-service/</guid>
      <description>If you want to subscribe to variable change in Angular 4 service or Angular 5 service, you can use something called the BehaviorSubject from the rxjs library. A behavior subject is like an observable, except that it must be created with an initial value as it is must always return a value even if the subject hasn&amp;#8217;t been updated. A behavior subject will always emit it&amp;#8217;s first value as soon as it&amp;#8217;s described.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu install Hangs on Splash Screen Fix</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/ubuntu-install-hangs-splash-screen-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 04:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/ubuntu-install-hangs-splash-screen-fix/</guid>
      <description>When I was trying to install Ubuntu I experienced a very strange issue. The Ubuntu install hangs on splash screen for a very long time. I would select the option to try Ubuntu in the grub menu, and then I would get this strange screen with broken graphics. It looked like the graphics failed to load or something. The Ubuntu install freezes on that screen and would not advance.
I eventually found out that this issue will occur if you are using an Nvidia Graphics card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a Multiplayer game using Javascript</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/build-a-mmo-game-with-javascript-and-nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 22:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/build-a-mmo-game-with-javascript-and-nodejs/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we will take a look at how to build a multiplayer game using Javascript and NodeJS. My goal is to take you through the basic setup so that you can begin focusing on the actual gameplay. When building a full-scale MMO, there are a lot of things to consider like load balancing, network contingencies, etc. For now, we are going to focus on the bare minimum just to help you get an understanding of how you can creatively and effectively use the available tools of NodeJS to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Javascript Hashcash Proof of Work</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-hashcash-proof-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-hashcash-proof-work/</guid>
      <description>Suppose that you developed an app that will give users free stuff when they click a button. Obviously, there&amp;#8217;s nothing stopping one user from spamming the button one million times and collecting a whole bunch of free stuff. If you wanted to prevent that, you could use something like a CAPTCHA, or perhaps give each user a session and cool off period. You could also implement something called a proof of work system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a Javascript Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain! It&amp;#8217;s the mystical buzzword that every company is saying right now. At its core, the basic concept of blockchain is not hard to understand; it&amp;#8217;s essentially a distributed linked list. It&amp;#8217;s also used by the popular cryptocurrency called Bitcoin. The advantages of Blockchain is that it allows for a decentralized collection of data whose integrity is easily verifiable, and the data itself is immutable Keep in mind that a fully robust blockchain will also contain smart contracts, mining algorithms (proof of work/proof of stake) and other flavorful elements that you could enhance the chain with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Pixel 2 XL vs Galaxy Note 8</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/google-pixel-2-xl-vs-galaxy-note-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 17:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/google-pixel-2-xl-vs-galaxy-note-8/</guid>
      <description>The Google Pixel 2 XL and the Galaxy Note 8 are two excellent devices. They are so good, that I would be lying if I told you that it was easy to make a decision between these two devices. Deciding which one to buy is going to come down to a lot of personal preference and trivial differences. So let&amp;#8217;s do a comparison of the Google Pixel 2 XL vs Galaxy Note 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigate in ReactJS using React V4 Router</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/navigate-in-reactjs-using-react-v4-router/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 13:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/navigate-in-reactjs-using-react-v4-router/</guid>
      <description>If you are building a large single page application, there might come a time when you will need to add routes to different pages. Unlike traditional routes, adding routes in ReactJS does not trigger a page reload. This makes your SPA extremely fast and feels more like an actual application rather than a simple website. To navigate in ReactJS we will be using the React v4 router.
Setting Up React V4 Router Begin by installing the React V4 Router from npm:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the JavaScript Spread Operator</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/understanding-the-javascript-spread-operator-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 05:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/understanding-the-javascript-spread-operator-2/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;#8217;s a good chance that you have probably come across the Javascript spread operator. If you are unsure, here&amp;#8217;s what it looks like:
{...} Good luck trying to google search that as you will probably get an empty results page. The Javascript spread operator is a new syntax found in ES6 (ECMAScript2015). The purpose of the spread operator is to allow an iterable like an array or string to be expanded (or spread) across another object or array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the JavaScript Spread Operator</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/understanding-the-javascript-spread-operator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 05:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/understanding-the-javascript-spread-operator/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;#8217;s a good chance that you have probably come across the Javascript spread operator. If you are unsure, here&amp;#8217;s what it looks like:
{...} Good luck trying to google search that as you will probably get an empty results page. The Javascript spread operator is a new syntax found in ES6 (ECMAScript2015). The purpose of the spread operator is to allow an iterable like an array or string to be expanded (or spread) across another object or array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Kali Linux 2 on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-kali-linux-2-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 03:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-kali-linux-2-android/</guid>
      <description>Kali Linux is a popular security-focused operating system that has many tools which could be used for penetration testing. In the past, I demonstrated how to Run Kali Linux on Android (version 1.0) via the terminal. Now let&amp;#8217;s take a look at how to run Kali Linux 2 on Android without root. To do this, we will be using Limbo PC Emulator. It makes use of the SDL library to emulate Kali Linux 2 on Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multithreaded Javascript</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/multithreaded-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 15:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/multithreaded-javascript/</guid>
      <description>For the longest time, Javascript has always been implemented using a single thread in your browser. For the most part, this wasn&amp;#8217;t a problem. If you&amp;#8217;re just using javascript for simple DOM manipulations or form submissions then a single thread is all you need. However, once developers started getting more advanced with their Javascript usage, this eventually led to an issue.
Let&amp;#8217;s say I have the following single page application (SPA) that shows a list of prime numbers from 1 to 600,000:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Android Nougat on PC</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-android-nougat-on-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 02:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-android-nougat-on-pc/</guid>
      <description>Do you have an old computer laying around that you need to find a use for? How about running Android Nougat on your PC? The Android x86 team has successfully ported Android 7.1 over to the desktop CPU architecture. This means you can enjoy your favorite apps and games on any pc or laptop.
Run Android Nougat on PC The first thing that you need to do is download the Android Nougat x86 ISO file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning in Javascript</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/machine-learning-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 17:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/machine-learning-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;#8217;s a good chance that you don&amp;#8217;t think of JavaScript when you think of artificial intelligence and machine learning. Instead, you might think of Python and popular libraries like Google&amp;#8217;s Tensorflow. While TensorFlow is very powerful and complex, it does require a steep learning curve. Personally, I&amp;#8217;m just looking to get my feet wet in some simple AI programming. However, I came across a javascript library called Brain.js. This library makes machine learning in javascript plausible and testable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Read USB</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-read-usb-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 17:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-read-usb-2/</guid>
      <description>You can now officially use JavaScript to read USB devices that are connected to your computer. This is using the new WebUSB API that is still in early draft. As being so, the API could later change or be removed altogether until it receives the final verification.
In order to use WebUSB you need to be running the latest version of Google Chrome, with the experimental web platform features flag enabled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapchat using Javascript – Zuck.js</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/snapchat-using-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/snapchat-using-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Stories! Stories are everywhere these days. Snapchat, Instagram, Facebook, Facebook Messenger and Whatsapp all have stories. Hell, it&amp;#8217;s only a matter of time before Microsoft Excel gets a stories update.
&amp;nbsp;

In any case, if you want to build an app like Snapchat or build an app like Instagram, there is an easy way to do so. The focus of this tutorial will be about building the story functionality of Snapchat and Instagram into an app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reddit API Application only OAuth in Javascript</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/reddit-api-application-oauth-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 17:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/reddit-api-application-oauth-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Before you begin developing your Reddit application, you will need to make sure that your app is authorized to access the Reddit API. Authorization is done through OAuth tokens that you receive from the Reddit server. The flow is pretty straightforward:
 Application Requests Token App Receives Token that&amp;#8217;s valid for an hour App makes API calls with given token App request new token when the previous token expires  For this tutorial, we are going to build a simple app that grabs the new posts from a subreddit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run any OS on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-os-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-os-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>If Chrome OS is not fulfilling your needs, all hope isn&amp;#8217;t lost. You can run any OS on a Chromebook as long as it has an x86 processor (Chromebooks with an Intel Processor). That means you can run Windows on your Chromebook or even run Mint Linux on your Chromebook.
You will need to have developer mode enabled on your Chromebook  Run Any OS on Chromebook In order to run any OS on your Chromebook, you will have to enable the legacy bios with USB booting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Windows from Compressing Wallpaper</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stop-windows-from-compressing-wallpaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 13:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stop-windows-from-compressing-wallpaper/</guid>
      <description>By default, Windows compresses your desktop wallpaper by up to 85% of its original quality. This is done to maximize performance because most people don&amp;#8217;t need a 50 MB image eating up precious RAM. There are two methods that you can use to stop Windows from compressing wallpapers. The first (unconfirmed) method is to use a PNG image file. There have been some reports that on the latest Windows 10 Creator&amp;#8217;s update, PNG images are immune to Windows compression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Theme any App</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/dark-theme-any-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 13:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/dark-theme-any-app/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love dark themes in my apps. Not only is it easier on the eyes, but having a true amoled black theme could save you battery life on certain devices like the Galaxy S8. Unfortunately, not every app comes with a dark theme option. So if you want to dark theme any app on your device you will need to use the theme engine called Substratum. Substratum could give you a dark theme Instagram, dark them Facebook, dark theme Inbox, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Read USB</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-read-usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 13:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-read-usb/</guid>
      <description>You can now officially use JavaScript to read USB devices that are connected to your computer. This is using the new WebUSB API that is still in early draft. As being so, the API could later change or be removed altogether until it receives the final verification.
In order to use WebUSB you need to be running the latest version of Google Chrome, with the experimental web platform features flag enabled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Callbacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-callbacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 02:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/javascript-callbacks/</guid>
      <description>In Javascript, a callback function is a function that is passed into another function as an argument. This allows you to invoke that function with a return value. Remember, Javascript&amp;#8217;s implementation within a browser is single threaded (well..until recently at least). That means that all of your code is executed within one linear operation. However, there are some functions in Javascript which are asynchronous. That means that they have the privilege to be invoked anywhere in that line of execution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overclock Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/overclock-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/overclock-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Overclock Chromebook? It sounds like something that should be impossible to do. However, with the power of Linux, everything is possible. The Chromebook doesn&amp;#8217;t have the typical bios that you would find on a standard PC. Therefore, you can&amp;#8217;t easily change the CPU frequency. Using Linux, we can achieve a software FSB overclock or underclock. For this tutorial, let&amp;#8217;s focus on underclocking because that&amp;#8217;s the easier thing to do (damn that click bait).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Echo Show Web Browser</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/amazon-echo-show-web-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 01:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/amazon-echo-show-web-browser/</guid>
      <description>The Amazon Echo Show has a hidden web browser, and here is how you can enable it. Keep in mind that the Amazon Echo Show is running Android at its core. Therefore, like any normal Android web browser, you have access to the same WebKit features and vulnerabilities when using the browser.
Enable Amazon Echo Show Web Browser Go into your settings and go to Legal and Compliance.
Then go into Amazon Privacy Notice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Freeform Mode</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-freeform-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 19:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-freeform-mode/</guid>
      <description>Android Freeform mode is a new hidden feature in Android Nougat (7.0). According to the Android developer guide, &amp;#8220;Manufacturers of larger devices can choose to enable freeform mode, in which the user can freely resize each activity. If the manufacturer enables this feature, the device offers freeform mode in addition to split-screen mode.&amp;#8221; Although the developer guides species larger devices, this could be enabled on smaller devices as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Kali Linux on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-kali-linux-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-kali-linux-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Kali Linux is a popular security focused operating system. It offers a lot of&amp;#8230;eh&amp;#8230;&amp;#8221;interesting&amp;#8221; use case scenarios. To install Kali Linux on the Chromebook is very easy. Crouton (the popular open source script that is used to install other operating systems on the Chromebook such as Ubuntu on Chromebook) can be used to install Kali Linux on Chromebook.
Before you begin! You will need to have developer mode enabled on your Chromebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play 4K YouTube Videos on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-4k-youtube-videos-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 23:38:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-4k-youtube-videos-android/</guid>
      <description>So we have these impressive ultra-high resolution smartphones, yet we still can&amp;#8217;t seem to play 4k youtube videos on Android. Some devices can&amp;#8217;t even play 1440p YouTube videos despite having the appropriate screen resolution. Luckily, there is a simple trick that you can do to get a higher resolution format via the YouTube app on your phone, even if your screen resolution is not 4k. Essentially, we are going to add a line to the build prop that &amp;#8220;tricks&amp;#8221; the YouTube app into thinking you have a different display size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android WiFi Jammer</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-wifi-jammer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 03:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-wifi-jammer/</guid>
      <description>For less than $10, you can have an Android WiFI Jammer up and running. To get started, you are going to need to have the NodeMCU. It&amp;#8217;s a WiFI development chip that&amp;#8217;s usually used in Raspberry Pi and Arduino projects. However, the chip can also be used as a standalone device (it has its own CPU and memory) as long as you give it sufficient power. This means you can power it through another Android phone, your computer, power bank or any device that&amp;#8217;s capable of supplying power over USB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable Developer Mode on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/developer-mode-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 14:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/developer-mode-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>If you want to get root acess or install Linux or Windows on your Chromebook at some point, then you will need to enable Developer Mode on Chromebook. To Enable Developer mode on Chromebook is very easy and only takes a few minutes.
This will erase all of your data on your Chromebook. Get Started Start at your homescreen and hold the following keys:
ESC + Refresh (F3) + POWER Your screen will briefly turn off before coming back on again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Linux on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/remove-linux-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 13:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/remove-linux-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Tired of crouton? If you installed Linux on your Chromebook using the crouton installer and you’re ready to delete it, here&amp;#8217;s how to remove Linux on Chromebook.
Super Simple On your Chromebook, open up the Chrome browser. Then open up the terminal by typing in the following:
CRTL + ALT + T Inside of the terminal, type in:
shell Finally, type in the following command to delete Linux from your Chromebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Linux on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-linux-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 13:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-linux-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Tired of Chrome OS? Do you want to play games like Minecraft or Steam Games on your Chromebook? Luckily, Linux allows you to accomplish some of that. To install Linux on Chromebook, we are going to use the crouton script. The script takes care of all of the downloading and configuration. All you need to do is run a couple of commands.
You need to make sure that you have developer mode enabled on your chromebook before attempting this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Actually Cool Android Tricks</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/5-actually-cool-android-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 23:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/5-actually-cool-android-tricks/</guid>
      <description>Here are 5 actually cool Android tricks that you can try on your device. A couple of these tricks will require that you have adb installed on your computer. None of these tricks require root.
Hide Soft Keys Softkeys are usually convenient to have but can eat up precious screen real estate. Unfortunately, not many android developers give users to ability to use their app in immersive mode (which autohides the softkeys).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi Webserver</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/raspberry-pi-webserver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 00:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/raspberry-pi-webserver/</guid>
      <description>One of the reasons that I purchased a Raspberry Pi was so that I can do local website development. Of course, I could have easily set this all up with Windows, but my desktop is already cluttered enough. And with a Raspberry Pi Webserver, I can set up scipts to run independently of my desktop. Here&amp;#8217;s how to setup a Raspberry Pi Webserver
What You Will Need:  Raspberry Pi  Setup Static IP Address It would be very annoying to have a website that always changes its address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete Pi User on Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/delete-pi-user-on-raspberry-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 00:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/delete-pi-user-on-raspberry-pi/</guid>
      <description>One of the first things you should do when setting up the Raspberry Pi is to change the default password for the pi user. Personally, I would rather just delete the user altogether and create my own user. So here&amp;#8217;s how I deleted the Pi user on Raspberry Pi.
Make sure that you backup any important data from your Pi user that you might need.  Step 1: Create a New User Before you begin, make sure that you can SSH into your Raspberry Pi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change NavBar Color Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/change-navbar-color-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 13:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/change-navbar-color-android/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;#8217;t like when OEM Skins change the Android Navbar Color. I like the Android Navbar color to always be black. It goes well with most apps and is easy on the eyes at night. Unfortunately, LG made the default color an ugly off white/gray. Using an app called Navbar apps, you can change the Android navigation bar color.
Link: https://goo.gl/Rt6myl</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Raspberry Pi 3</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/setup-raspberry-pi-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 01:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/setup-raspberry-pi-3/</guid>
      <description>The Raspberry Pi 3 is an excellent device for those who want the power of a full desktop with the footprint of a small mobile device. Setting up the raspberry Pi 3 is very easy and only takes 15 minutes.
What you will need:  Raspberry Pi 3 MicroSD Card (Preferably class 10 or higher) Micro USB Cable and Charger Ethernet Cable (Unless you want to use WiFi) HDMI Cable  Setup Raspberry Pi 3 There are a couple of different operating system that you could use on the Raspberry Pi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LG G6 Unboxing</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g6-unboxing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 15:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g6-unboxing/</guid>
      <description>The LG G6 is a phone with little bezel and lots of curves. The rounded corners of the LG G6 look nice but definitely take some time to get used to. Is the LG G6 better than the Samsung Galaxy S8? Who will win the ultimate battle of LG G6 vs Samsung Galaxy S8? Only time will tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-reverse-tether/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 19:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-reverse-tether/</guid>
      <description>There might come a time when you need to access the internet from your phone, but you don&amp;#8217;t have access to WiFi or mobile data. When that happens, Android Reverse Tether would be a useful thing to know. Reverse tethering means to share your computer internet connection with your phone (rather than the other way around). There are a couple of ways that you can do it. One way is to create a WiFi hotspot from your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install ADB</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-adb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 18:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-adb/</guid>
      <description>The Android Development Bridge (ADB) is a vital part of Android App development, along with Android modding. Learning how to install ADB can help you later down the line. ADB allows you to access your Android phone via USB and issue commands to it. This can be really helpful for flashing roms, automated scripts or if your device is inaccessible through the normal Android interface. For this tutorial, we are going to focus on how to install ADB on Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No More Internet Privacy</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/no-more-internet-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 21:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/no-more-internet-privacy/</guid>
      <description>This video is different that my usual content. In light of recent events, I wanted to highlight some of the concerns of privacy that is being challenged through companies and congress. I don&amp;#8217;t want to persuade you either way, but I just want to make you an informed consumer as to what&amp;#8217;s going on. There has been the recent incident of Verizon installing spyware on Android devices and the repeal of internet privacy laws (S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Linux Apps</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-linux-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 15:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-linux-apps/</guid>
      <description>I spent a couple of months using Linux as my secondary operating system. During that time, I came across some really useful Linux apps that satisfied my needs. So here&amp;#8217;s my list of the top Linux Apps.
HTOP To view the running tasks in Linux, all you need to do is open up a terminal window and type in the command top. This will give you a quick running view of all the active processes on your system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheapest Computer You Can Buy</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/cheapest-computer-can-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 03:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/cheapest-computer-can-buy/</guid>
      <description>If you are in the market for a computer that will cost you about the same price as a large Starbucks iced coffee, then you are at the right place. Introducing, the Raspberry Pi Zero W. The Raspberry Pu Zero W is the cheapest computer you can buy. This computer isn&amp;#8217;t made for gaming or bitcoin mining. It&amp;#8217;s aimed at developers and enthusiasts to use in their projects. It would also make for a great setup for a small home server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s new in Android O?</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/whats-new-android-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 02:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/whats-new-android-o/</guid>
      <description>Google has just released the details of Android 0, the next version of Android. So what&amp;#8217;s new in Android O? You can find an overview of all the features over on the Android developer website. However, I want to share my favorite features slated to be in Android O.
App Auto Fill Framework This new app autofill framework will allow users to select an app as their fill app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dual Boot Windows 10 and Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/dual-boot-windows-10-and-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 02:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/dual-boot-windows-10-and-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>I woke up Sunday Morning with a cool project in mind. I wanted to dual boot Windows 10 and Ubuntu. The real reason for this was because I decided to give Jekyll a try and it was going to be my replacement for WordPress, but I digress. Another major reason to dual-boot Windows 10 and Ubuntu was so that I could keep all of my Android development and Web development stuff within Ubuntu and use Windows solely for video editing and gaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Android Apps March 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-7-android-apps-march-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 22:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-7-android-apps-march-2017/</guid>
      <description>Here is my pick for top 7 Android apps for March 2017.
Energy Bar No this is not a snack. This app will display your battery level as a small line above your status bar. You can adjust the thickness and position of the line. At first it&amp;#8217;s kinda distracting to look at, however, I&amp;#8217;m quickly getting used it; I just love how subtle it is. I also think it&amp;#8217;s easier to estimate my battery using this rather than looking at the battery icon in the status bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control your Android Phone without Touching It</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/control-android-phone-without-touching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 04:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/control-android-phone-without-touching/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for something cool to try, then download Eva Facial Mouse. This app allows you to control your android phone using your face. Using your face as an anchor point, the app moves the cursor on your phone relative to that point. Essentially, you are using your face to control the mouse pointer. While this is not something you should use in a practical setup, it&amp;#8217;s still a cool app to show off to your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Steam Games to Android 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-android-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 02:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-android-2017/</guid>
      <description>If all Android phones came with DirectX and desktop graphics, then playing native games would be a breeze. Unfortautnetly, that is far from the case. So while you might not be able to play Fallout 4 on android, there is nothing stopping you from streaming it to your device. Here&amp;#8217;s how you can Stream Steams Games to Android.
What You Will Need:  Nvidia 600 series or better graphics Card GeForce Experience App Moonlight  If your graphics card doesn&amp;#8217;t fit the requirements, then check out my other tutorial on how to Stream Steam Games to Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replace Chrome OS with Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/replace-chrome-os-with-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 22:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/replace-chrome-os-with-windows/</guid>
      <description>I love Chrome OS but I also realize that it&amp;#8217;s pretty useless without an internet connection. Okay&amp;#8230;maybe not pretty useless but _mostly useless._ I can&amp;#8217;t game, program or do anything useful on Chrome OS other than browse the web. Luckily, if you are using a Chromebook with an Intel CPU (sorry Samsung Chromebook users) you can replace Chrome OS with Windows. Previously, I did a tutorial on How to install Windows on a Chromebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Shared Network Folder Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/create-shared-network-folde-linux-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 16:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/create-shared-network-folde-linux-r/</guid>
      <description>One of the most convenient ways to share data across a network is using a shared network folder. In Windows, setting up a shared network is usually an easy process. However, it&amp;#8217;s not a straightforward to do in Linux (no surprise).
Create Shared Network Folder Linux To begin, you are going to need to download and install samba
apt-get install samba apt-get install samba-common-bin Next, create the folder that you want to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Pokemon on Android Smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-pokemon-android-smartwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 16:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-pokemon-android-smartwatch/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever thought about playing Pokemon on your Android Wear Smartwatch? Neither have I. However, an app called Wear GBC makes this all possible. It is a Gameboy color emulator for Android Wear.
How to Play Pokemon on Android Smartwatch Here&amp;#8217;s a quick tutorial on how I got this up and running. First download a GBC ROM (.gbc). Then add it via the phone app (you might have to unzip it first if it&amp;#8217;s in a zip file).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share Internet Connection Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/share-internet-connection-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 16:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/share-internet-connection-windows/</guid>
      <description>My friend and I decided to have a small LAN gaming session the other day. There was just one problem, he didn&amp;#8217;t have a wireless adapter for his PC. Luckily, I had my Windows Surface on me and was able to share my internet through that (with the help of this USB Ethernet dongle) to my friend&amp;#8217;s PC.
To share your internet in Windows, you will need to make sure that you have a device that has an active wireless connection along with an Ethernet port.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Android Smartwatch 2016</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-android-smartwatch-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 15:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-android-smartwatch-2016/</guid>
      <description>I have been using the Huawei Watch for over two months now and I can safely say that it&amp;#8217;s the best Android smartwatch that I have ever owned. It features a high-quality aluminum design with a crisp 400 x 400 AMOLED display. There&amp;#8217;s even a speaker so that you can make phone calls and listen to music right from the watch. The only two things that I don&amp;#8217;t like about this watch is the weak vibration motor and the annoying pin charging mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Android Holiday Apps</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-android-holiday-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 15:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-android-holiday-apps/</guid>
      <description>   Weather Timeline Reuters TV (Sponsored) Circle Sidebar Google Photoscan  GeoQpons Krazy Coupon Lady Dingless </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Extensions for Google Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-extensions-google-chrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-extensions-google-chrome/</guid>
      <description>The best thing about Google Chrome is all the extensions that are available for it. Now I recently learned that Microsoft Edge also has extensions, but nowhere near as many as google chrome. By no means is this an exhaustive list of all the best extensions for Google Chrome; just a few of my favorites that I use every day.
Ghostery 
If you are concerned about your privacy on the internet, then Ghostery is the perfect app for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a VPN Server</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/create-a-vpn-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 01:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/create-a-vpn-server/</guid>
      <description>There are three routes that you can take when setting up a VPN. You can either use a free one, buy a paid service or make your own. The advantage of free VPNs is that they are easy to setup; just install and they are ready to be used. My favorite VPN on Android is Opera VPN. The downside of Free VPNs is that they typically come with a 500 &amp;#8211; 1GB data cap and are very slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measure Battery Usage in Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/measure-battery-usage-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 15:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/measure-battery-usage-windows/</guid>
      <description>Most people would never guess that there is a tool to measure battery usage in Windows. I first discovered this when trying to figure out what was draining my battery on my Surface Pro 3. For a quick overview of battery drain by app, you can use the Windows Battery Saving settings.
Windows Battery Saver To access this, type in Windows Battery Saver in the Start Menu search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Battery Saving Tips – Restrict Snapchat Background Data</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-battery-saving-tips-disable-snapchat-background-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-battery-saving-tips-disable-snapchat-background-data/</guid>
      <description>Battery life on Android is a nightmare to deal with unless you know exactly what to look for. Android&amp;#8217;s vague battery statistics can be frustrating for a novice and seasoned user alike. For example, a battery drain labeled as Android System could be Google Play Services performing something in the background, or the Facebook app using the camera, or any other app that makes any API call. And speaking of Facebook, there&amp;#8217;s a lot of conflicting research and anecdotal reports on whether the app is responsible for any sort of excessive battery drain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Cortana use Google</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/make-cortana-use-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 04:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/make-cortana-use-google/</guid>
      <description>As you know, Microsoft Cortana has become an integral part of Windows 10. I wouldn&amp;#8217;t mind Cortana so much if Microsoft didn&amp;#8217;t force it upon us. One thing which really bothers me about Cortana is that it defaults to Microsoft Edge and Bing. I am a Google person, so I would prefer if it used Google Search and Google Chrome. Before the Windows 10 Anniversary update, there used to be a way to change the default behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control Multiple Computers</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/control-multiple-computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 21:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/control-multiple-computers/</guid>
      <description>Does your workstation setup contain more than one computer? I have my main desktop along with my surface setting in front of my at all times. I sometimes hate that I have to reach across my desk and switch between keyboards to type something. Luckily, USB sharing between the two devices is not difficult. Thanks to a garage app by Microsoft, you can control multiple computers with one mouse and keyboard very easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar Watch</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/calendar-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 22:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/calendar-watch/</guid>
      <description>This is the Calendar Watch. It is a smartwatch by the company What? The Calendar Watch provides a unique take on smartwatches while adding in a good amount of luxury.
Enter in the Calendar Watch Giveaway Below: Calendar Watch Giveaway
**Open to anywhere that can physically receive packages from the U.S.**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play PlayStation 3 Games on PC</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-playstation-3-games-on-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-playstation-3-games-on-pc/</guid>
      <description>Although the PlayStation 4 is the latest console from Sony, the PlayStation 3 is still a popular game system that is enjoyed by many. One group of developers have been actively working to bring the PlayStation 3 experience to your PC. RPCS3 is an open source PlayStation 3 emulator. The emulator is still in early alpha stages, so don&amp;#8217;t expect many commercial titles to be compatible. It works well with homebrew games and games which do not require advanced 3D graphics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moto Z Play vs Oneplus 3</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/moto-z-play-vs-oneplus-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 03:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/moto-z-play-vs-oneplus-3/</guid>
      <description>Watch this hands-on comparison of the Moto Z Play vs Oneplus 3 and decide which device is better for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moto Z Play Review</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/moto-z-play-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 14:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/moto-z-play-review/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a phone that will give you the best battery life? If so, the $450 unlocked Moto Z Play is what you need. Check out this video of the Moto Z Play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Android Actual Battery Capacity</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/actual-android-battery-capacity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 23:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/actual-android-battery-capacity/</guid>
      <description>You might think that your battery is fine, but your capacity could be less than when you first bought it. What is your android actual battery capacity?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moto Z Play Unboxing</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/moto-z-play-unboxing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 13:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/moto-z-play-unboxing/</guid>
      <description>An Unboxing of the Moto Z Play. Motorola&amp;#8217;s surprisingly good mid-Range smartphone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Note 7 Discontinued</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-note-7-discontinued/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 00:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-note-7-discontinued/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s over. The Galaxy Note 7 is discontinued. So what should we expect now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Pixel Phone Disappointment</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/google-pixel-phone-disappointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 03:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/google-pixel-phone-disappointment/</guid>
      <description>Google has announced their new phone, the Pixel. It&amp;#8217;s coming off the heels of the forever loved Nexus program. IMO, this new Google Phone is asking too much while offering too little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kodi on Firestick</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/kodi-on-firestick/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 14:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/kodi-on-firestick/</guid>
      <description>Kodi on Firestick? Kodi (formerly XMBC) is a very popular platform for video entertainment that is designed to work on almost all operating systems. Previously, I shown how you can get Kodi on the Chromebook. You can also install Kodi on Android and Windows. For this tutorial, let&amp;#8217;s take a look at how to install Kodi on the Amazon Firestick.
The Easy Way: If you have an Android device, do yourself a favor and use this method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do we need imessage for Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/need-imessage-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 03:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/need-imessage-android/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has been talking about having an iMessage for Android. With the recent release of Google Allo, many people were disappointed that Allo did not have SMS fallback? But, do we really need an iMessage for Android?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Android as Microphone</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/use-android-as-microphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 15:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/use-android-as-microphone/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever needed a microphone, but did not have one available? Have you ever searched for a way to make a cheap wireless microphone? Needless to say, you can use your Android device as a microphone. There are two ways that this can be accomplished. The first is through traditional cables, and the second is through additional software. If you want to use your Android device as a microphone through USB, Wifi or Bluetooth, then skip to the second method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android cSploit</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-csploit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 15:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-csploit-2/</guid>
      <description>A little while ago, there was this awesome program called dSploit. It was a network security app that provided users with an abundance of tools and operations to test the strength of their network security. Recently, dSploit was merged with a proprietary closed source app that isn&amp;#8217;t free. While you can find older copies of dSploit floating around on the internet, none of them are up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android cSploit</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-csploit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 15:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-csploit/</guid>
      <description>A little while ago, there was this awesome program called dSploit. It was a network security app that provided users with an abundance of tools and operations to test the strength of their network security. Recently, dSploit was merged with a proprietary closed source app that isn&amp;#8217;t free. While you can find older copies of dSploit floating around on the internet, none of them are up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Note 7 Exploding</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-note-7-exploding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 14:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-note-7-exploding/</guid>
      <description>Samsung has recalled Galaxy Note 7 devices world wide due to incidents of explosion. What causes these devices and other Lithium-ion batteries to malfunction?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux in Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/linux-in-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/linux-in-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has done something really cool in the Windows 10 Anniversary Update. They gave users the ability to use the Linux Bash Command Line from within Windows. This is not through a virtual machine nor container, but a subsystem that they previously added in an earlier Windows update. Here&amp;#8217;s how you can enable Linux in Windows 10:
What You Will Need:  Windows 10 Anniversary Update  How To: ­</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Android as Second Monitor</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/use-android-as-second-monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/use-android-as-second-monitor/</guid>
      <description>Having more than one monitor is useful for any power user (porn on one, games on another). So it&amp;#8217;s possible to use an android device as a secondary monitor, but I recommend actually buying one if you want an easy setup. With that said, if you have a spare Android device laying around, you can use it as another monitor in your setup. To do this, we are going to use Windows and &amp;#8220;trick&amp;#8221; it into thinking that you have another monitor connected and then use TeamViewer to access the &amp;#8220;fake&amp;#8221; monitor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oneplus 3 Review</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/oneplus-3-review-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 14:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/oneplus-3-review-2/</guid>
      <description>After using the Oneplus for a week, I want to share my opinion of the device. Mainly focusing on the things that I really liked about it and the things that I didn&amp;#8217;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oneplus 3 Review</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/oneplus-3-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 14:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/oneplus-3-review/</guid>
      <description>After using the Oneplus for a week, I want to share my opinion of the device. Mainly focusing on the things that I really liked about it and the things that I didn&amp;#8217;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oneplus 3 Unboxing</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/oneplus-3-unboxing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 14:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/oneplus-3-unboxing/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s unbox the Oneplus 3!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USB Condom &amp; MicFlip</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/usb-condom-micflip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 14:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/usb-condom-micflip/</guid>
      <description>So here is some interesting tech under $25 that I have been using.
USB Condom: https://goo.gl/HkUacx
MicFlip: https://goo.gl/Ui7fkb</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Samsung Galaxy Apps</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-samsung-galaxy-android-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 14:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-samsung-galaxy-android-apps/</guid>
      <description>Here is my pick for some of the most useful Samsung Galaxy apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/reverse-tether/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 13:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/reverse-tether/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever been stuck in a situation that you needed WiFi but only had an Ethernet connection available? Unless you&amp;#8217;re looking to connect your phone to an Ethernet connection, you would be all out of options. I found myself in a similar situation when I needed to setup a live stream using a bunch of laptops and only one Ethernet connection with no WiFi available. This is also useful if you are looking to avoid using mobile data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s on my Phone</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/whats-on-my-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 14:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/whats-on-my-phone/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;#8217;s on my phone? I want to share with you some of the Android apps that I use on my phone everyday.
Android Customization:  Nova Launcher Iride UI is Hipster Zooper Widget Zooper Widget Theme  Productivity:  Google Keep Todoist Inbox Evernote Calendar Widget  Texting:  Textra  Social:  Buffer Fenix Sync for Reddit  &amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hearthstone on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/hearthstone-on-chromebook-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 20:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/hearthstone-on-chromebook-2/</guid>
      <description>Hearthstone is a very popular game which I coincidentally don&amp;#8217;t play. However, I do spend quite a lot of time on my Chromebook and love seeing how far I can push its compatibility with software. Naturally, the idea of running Hearthstone on Chromebook appealed to me. After all, Counter Strike, TeamFortress and PlayStation 2 games work, so I don&amp;#8217;t see why Hearthstone wouldn&amp;#8217;t.
If you haven&amp;#8217;t guessed already, we are going to be using Linux to make this work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hearthstone on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/hearthstone-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 20:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/hearthstone-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Hearthstone is a very popular game which I coincidentally don&amp;#8217;t play. However, I do spend quite a lot of time on my Chromebook and love seeing how far I can push its compatibility with software. Naturally, the idea of running Hearthstone on Chromebook appealed to me. After all, Counter Strike, TeamFortress and PlayStation 2 games work, so I don&amp;#8217;t see why Hearthstone wouldn&amp;#8217;t.
If you haven&amp;#8217;t guessed already, we are going to be using Linux to make this work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Least Used Android Features</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/least-used-android-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 14:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/least-used-android-features/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of cool features on Android, but you might not actually have a use for them. Here are some of my least used features of Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>League on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/league-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 15:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/league-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>I have received many requests to do a video of League on Chromebook. Well, it shouldn&amp;#8217;t be too surprising that it works. All it takes is running Windows on your Chromebook. The biggest limitation that I face was the insufficient hard drive space on my Chromebook (Acer C720). To solve that issue, I installed League to a flash drive. Of course, this had a negative effect on the game&amp;#8217;s load time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save Battery Life on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/save-battery-life-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 14:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/save-battery-life-android/</guid>
      <description>Every year, smartphones get better and better. We live in the age where the average smartphone has better specs than a two year old computer. Despite all of this technological innovation, battery life is still a major concern for many consumers. It&amp;#8217;s simple, we need longer lasting batteries. Unfortunately, until there is a scientific breakthrough with battery technology, this is unlikely to change. Fortunately, there is a way that you can get the most out of your battery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack Android Apps and Games</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/hack-android-apps-and-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 14:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/hack-android-apps-and-games/</guid>
      <description>Wouldn&amp;#8217;t it be great if every game had cheat codes? Well, this might be closer than you think. Using the app Game Guardian, we can change the value of any numerical data within Android games. Yes, you can now achieve an unbeatable high score in your favorite game.
To do this you will need to have a rooted Android device. The process for this is fairly simple. We need to find the location of the desired attribute then change its value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Windows 7 on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-windows-7-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-windows-7-android/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;#8217;t believe I&amp;#8217;m saying it, but you can run Windows 7 on your Android device. To be honest, I was convinced that running Windows XP on Android would be the final step in Windows emulation, but I was wrong. Before you get too excited about playing the latest AAA title on your phone, keep in mind that this is nothing further than a proof of concept. The performance is painfully sluggish and the app might crash if Windows starts using too much memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallout 4 Tribute</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/fallout-4-tribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 14:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/fallout-4-tribute/</guid>
      <description>So I had some leftover Fallout 4 footage lying around and I came across Lune by NCS. I feel like this song would be the perfect soundtrack for this game. So here&amp;#8217;s a short video montage of a few action shots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Keyboard</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/laser-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/laser-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>Are laser keyboards the new thing?
AGS Laser Keyboard: http://goo.gl/DItpbm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counter Strike on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/counter-strike-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/counter-strike-android/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
How would you like to play one of the most popular PC games of all time on your Android device? So, maybe playing Half-Life 2 and Team-Fortress classic on Android isn&amp;#8217;t cool enough for you. Well, how about Counter Strike on Android? Of course, this isn&amp;#8217;t going to be the latest Counter Strike Global Offensive with the Source Engine. It&amp;#8217;s going to be the old school original counter strike from the late 90s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VPN Server on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/vpn-server-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 02:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/vpn-server-android/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#8217;re not using a VPN, you should consider using one. A Virtual Private Network (VPN) extends a private network across a public network. This gives you an added layer of security and privacy. Imagine if you are sitting at a Starbucks on their free public WiFi. Well, someone could have a program such as Wireshark or any other application open and sniff traffic across the network. Potentially, information such as usernames, passwords and other sensitive data could be exposed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>College Students try VR Horror and Porn</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/college-students-try-vr-horror-porn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 15:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/college-students-try-vr-horror-porn/</guid>
      <description>So I gathered a couple of friends to try out Virtual Reality Horror Games and of course porn. In the end, a bunch of laughter ensues.
VR Headets Used:
Grear VR: http://goo.gl/LgIkl5
Ling VR: http://goo.gl/3OQVPp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read Car Computer with Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/read-car-computer-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 15:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/read-car-computer-android/</guid>
      <description>You can use a bluetooth OBD II tool with your Android device to read important information from your car&amp;#8217;s computer and even see real time data.
OBD II: https://goo.gl/rQb68v
Torque App: https://goo.gl/UDNCDT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Features Android N</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-features-android-n/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 15:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-features-android-n/</guid>
      <description>The Android N Developer Preview has arrived. Here are some of the top new features you can find in Android N.
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer on Fire!</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/computer-fire-giveaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 15:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/computer-fire-giveaway/</guid>
      <description>My Computer Caught on Fire! Oh&amp;#8230;and here&amp;#8217;s a giveaway too.
Giveaway is now closed! Thanks to all who entered!
You can also purchase the 8000Mah ToughTested case here:
http://goo.gl/d4WlSH</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silent Boot Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/silent-boot-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 15:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/silent-boot-android/</guid>
      <description>I hate the carrier boot sound when restarting my phone. Here&amp;#8217;s how to boot without hearing it.
This video includes a Sponsored Message from Norton.
Check out Norton&amp;#8217;s The Most Dangerous Town Ep. 2 &amp;#8211; http://full.sc/MDT-OSG</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect Floppy Drive to Galaxy S7</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/connect-floppy-drive-galaxy-s7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 15:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/connect-floppy-drive-galaxy-s7/</guid>
      <description>Yes, you can connect a floppy drive to the Galaxy S7 or any Android device really. Just something random and simple I wanted to share. Of course&amp;#8230;I don&amp;#8217;t know why you would actually want to connect a floppy drive to your device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy S7 RAM Management</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s7-ram-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 15:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s7-ram-management/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;#8217;s a look at the Galaxy S7 RAM Management. Has Samsung improved over the S6&amp;#8217;s terribly aggressive memory management?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy S7 Features: Game Launcher</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s7-features-game-launcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 15:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s7-features-game-launcher/</guid>
      <description>The Galaxy S7 features a Game Launcher that is actually very convenient and easy to use while adding useful features during gameplay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy S7 Review – Don’t Buy into Hype</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s7-review-dont-buy-hype/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 15:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s7-review-dont-buy-hype/</guid>
      <description>The Galaxy S7 Review is here. Although I am very critical on Samsung&amp;#8217;s skin, I would say that the S7/S7 edge might be the best smartphone of 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy S7 Unboxing</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s7-unboxing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 17:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s7-unboxing/</guid>
      <description>A Galaxy S7 Unboxing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watercooling in Smartphones Explained</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/watercooling-smartphones-explained/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 17:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/watercooling-smartphones-explained/</guid>
      <description>How does watercooling work in Smartphones like the Galaxy S7?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Top Android Apps 2016</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-android-apps-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 17:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/top-android-apps-2016/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of the apps that I use everyday on my device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Root any Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/root-any-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 19:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/root-any-android/</guid>
      <description>I always get a lot of questions asking for instructions on how to root a particular device. Unfortunately, the root exploit that worked on one device might now work on another. This usually means that the user will have to spend hours searching for a method to root their device. This tasks becomes even more challenging if their device from a little known company without a development community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/mac-os-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 19:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/mac-os-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Do you ever come across some crazy ideas? Well, this is certainly one of them. Running Mac OS on Chromebook is a lot easier than you think. Now keep in mind, you aren&amp;#8217;t going to be able to do anything intensive on this. This is more a proof concept (like a lot of things that I do) and something just to admire.
To do this, we are going to be doing some very convoluted emulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remotely Turn on Computer with Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/remotely-turn-on-computer-with-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 22:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/remotely-turn-on-computer-with-linux/</guid>
      <description>I really wish more people used WOL. It is probably one of the most underrated things in the world of wired networking. If you aren&amp;#8217;t familiar, WOL (Wake on Lan) allows you to remotely turn on your computer. This could be from another computer or even your Android device. It works by supplying a little bit of power to your Ethernet card to allow it to listen for the &amp;#8220;wake up&amp;#8221; signal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-linux/</guid>
      <description>Now that you are familiar with Linux, how do you go about installing it? Well, the beauty of Linux is that there are many different flavors at your disposal, in the form of distributions. Each distribution offers its own pre-installed software and default desktop and environment. There are thousands of different Linux distributions to choose from. If you are looking for a distribution that fits your needs, check out this list of the top 11 best Linux distributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remix OS on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/remix-os-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 23:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/remix-os-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>It seems like everyone has been talking about Remix OS lately. If you aren&amp;#8217;t up to date, Remix OS is another implementation of the Android x86 poject. The goal of the project is to get Android running on desktops.
In the video above, I took a brief look at the state of Remix OS. The tl;dr is that it&amp;#8217;s well designed and offers a nice stylish edge over the normal stock Android UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Linux on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-linux-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 00:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-linux-on-android/</guid>
      <description>One of the coolest things that you could possibly do with your Android device is to run Linux on it (A full desktop operating system, in the palm of your hand). If you are asking yourself what Linux is exactly, this might help give you a quick explanation.
So what advantages would you get out of running Linux on your Android device? Well, besides doing things like running a Minecraft server and building your own cloud, you have a full suite of applications and&amp;#8230;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Kodi on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-kodi-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 04:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-kodi-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Kodi (formely Xbmc) has become a popular in-home media platform. Luckily, getting it on your Chromebook is not much of a challenge. However, you will need to make sure that you have Linux installed on your Chromebook first. Here&amp;#8217;s a short video on how to install Kodi on Chromebook.
Terminal commands:
sudo apt-get install software-properties-common sudo add-apt-repository ppa:team-xbmc/ppa sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install kodi </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a Supercomputer</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-a-supercomputer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 03:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-a-supercomputer/</guid>
      <description>So you want to build a supercomputer? Well, if you checked out my video on quantum computing you&amp;#8217;ll know that scientist are working to make computers stronger and faster than ever. Unfortunately, building a quantum computer is not something you can do at home, unless your home is a laboratory of course. All hope isn&amp;#8217;t lost though, you can still go on to build your very own supercomputer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Computer from Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-computer-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 16:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-computer-android/</guid>
      <description>Consider this, you are sitting across the room chilling on your couch and you&amp;#8217;re starting to fall asleep. Here&amp;#8217;s the problem, your couch feels so good and you don&amp;#8217;t want to get up to lock your computer, but you need to because you have nosy roommates. So wouldn&amp;#8217;t it be great if you could remotely lock it from your phone? Okay, so even if this situation is completely unbelievable, this is still something cool to try and do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cast Android Screen to PC</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/cast-android-screen-to-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 03:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/cast-android-screen-to-pc/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever had a moment where you wish that you could view a picture/video or even a game on a display larger than your phone? Maybe you haven&amp;#8217;t, but it&amp;#8217;s still something really cool to try it. This tutorial will take you through the basics on how to casts Android screen to PC.
Before we begin, I do want to mention that those of you who are using one of the latest Samsung phones already have this feature built in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallout 4 Tweaks</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/fallout-4-tweaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 16:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/fallout-4-tweaks/</guid>
      <description>Fallout 4 has been one of my favorite games of the year, but it isn&amp;#8217;t perfect. Everyone is aware how&amp;#8230;lacking&amp;#8230; Bethesda can be with their games. However, thanks to the modding community, many of the issues that you might encounter in Fallout 4 can be fixed.
One of the biggest complaints about Fallout 4 has been the FPS lock and not supporting 21:9 widescreen monitors. If you&amp;#8217;re feeling adventurous, you can dig through the game&amp;#8217;s ini file and adjust the values accordingly, but the easier solution would be to download the Fallout 4 Configuration tool which allows to you use a simple GUI that will make Fallout 4 tweaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect Android to Ethernet</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/connect-android-to-ethernet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 15:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/connect-android-to-ethernet/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to get the fastest speed available on your Android device? Sure, LTE is fast and all but you&amp;#8217;re hit with really small data caps. WiFi doesn&amp;#8217;t impose the same limitations, but the speed is never consistent. So why not just connect Android to Ethernet?
Luckily, Android Marshmallow comes to the rescue. Android Marshmallow introduces new drivers that allow you to connect your Android device directly to an Ethernet cable without needing root!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Steam Games Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 15:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Hopefully it is clear by now that Chromebooks are not meant for gaming of any type. However, that hasn&amp;#8217;t stopped many of you from accomplishing things like playing CS:GO on your Chromebook or PS2 Games. However, games like CS:GO and TF2 will work on almost any piece of hardware, but something like Fallout 4 won&amp;#8217;t.
If you&amp;#8217;re still determined to game from your Chromebook, you can do so via streaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ios Emojis on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/ios-emojis-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 15:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/ios-emojis-on-android/</guid>
      <description>Everyone loves those new iOS emojis. One annoying thing about dealing with emojis is that they look different on every platform. Android has the green blobs while ios has the yellow faces.
In any case, getting the new ios 90 emojis on your Android device is not that difficult, provided that you have a rooted Android device. Keep in mind though, this will only allow you to receive and interpret ios emojis on your device (so no more boxes with X&amp;#8217;s in them when you receive an emoji from your ios friend) but you will not be able to send the new emojis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Smash Bros Meele on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/super-smash-bros-meele-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 22:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/super-smash-bros-meele-on-android/</guid>
      <description>One of the best things about Android is that there are a lot of emulators for the platform. You can play games from the PS2, Nintendo DS, PSP, etc. No other mobile platform comes close to the same amount of emulation apps. With that said, one popular emulator that has been lurking around for quite some time is the Dolphin Emulator. It&amp;#8217;s capable of emulating GameCube and Wii games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Life 2 on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/half-life-2-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 19:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/half-life-2-on-android/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s talk about playing Half Life 2 on Android. If you are lucky enough to own an Nvidia Tegra device (such as the Shield) then you can completely ignore this tutorial because it doesn&amp;#8217;t apply to you. Half Life 2 exists as an exclusive for Nvidia&amp;#8217;s Shield device. Unfortunately, not everyone owns a device that is running the Tegra cpu. Luckily, using the app GlTools, you can emulate the Tegra graphics driver on your device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>League of Legends on Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/league-of-legends-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/league-of-legends-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>League players are everywhere. Sure, the majority of them are PC users, but there&amp;#8217;s a growing population of Linux gamers out there who want in on the action. Thanks to the program Play On Linux, which makes use of Wine (a popular program that allows many Windows applications to run on Linux), anyone can play League on their alinux computer.
I should also add that this procedure will also work on an x86 Chromebook with Crouton installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Chrome OS on PC</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-chrome-os-on-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 02:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-chrome-os-on-pc/</guid>
      <description>I recently came to the realization that Chrome OS is in some ways a perfect operating system. No, I swear I&amp;#8217;m not taking any hallucinogens. Here is a scenario that really opened my mind. I have an aunt who uses a basic low spec PC running Windows XP. All she does is check her email and check Facebook once per day, and that&amp;#8217;s it. Unfortunately, her PC barely meets the requirements to run Windows XP effectively and is constantly cluttered from maleware, Trojans, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Mac OS X Yosemite on any PC</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-mac-os-x-yosemite-on-any-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 01:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-mac-os-x-yosemite-on-any-pc/</guid>
      <description>I will be the first to admit that I prefer Windows over Mac OS any day. Besides being a slight Microsoft fanboy, I do prefer Windows because it meets all of my software and gaming needs, but I digress. In any case, there are still some unfortunate situations when I need to have access to Mac OS.
Luckily, I&amp;#8217;ll show you an easy way on how to install Mac OS X Yosemite on any pc, regardless of the hardware that you currently have installed (even if it is an AMD CPU).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Windows 10 from USB</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-windows-10-from-usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 20:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-windows-10-from-usb/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#8217;re looking for an ultra portable solution for your computing lifestyle, you might be interested in running Windows 10 from USB. It&amp;#8217;s a good solution if you do light work on multiple computers. Now clearly, this is not the most ideal situation. For one, this will surely shortness the life cycle of your USB with the numerous reads and writes it&amp;#8217;ll have to perform. Also, USB speed is much slower than SATA speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Half Life on Android Wear</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-half-life-on-android-wear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-half-life-on-android-wear/</guid>
      <description>Just because you can, doesn&amp;#8217;t mean you should. But in this case, you totally should. If you recall, I demonstrated how to play Team Fortress Classic on Android using the SDLash app. The app is able to emulate the GoldSource game engine, which was used in many of the classic valve games such as Half-Life and Team Fortress. Right now, I am putting together a tutorial on how to play Half-life on Android, but in the meantime, check out how to do it on Android Wear (albeit a little more complicated).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Minecraft Server on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-minecraft-server-on-chomebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 18:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-minecraft-server-on-chomebook/</guid>
      <description>So do you have a Chromebook sitting around that you have absolutely no idea what to do with? Well, if you or your buddies are minecraft junkies, then why not consider turning your Chromebook into a Minecraft server. It runs slightly faster than using your Android phone as a minecraft server, and offers a playable speed(though it can lag occasionally).
Now before you do this, you need to make sure that you have Ubuntu Installed on your Chromebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Team Fortress Classic on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-team-fortress-classic-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-team-fortress-classic-on-android/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever imagined that you would be able to play a Steam game on your phone? Well, I hope so, because I already demonstrated how to play Portal on your Android device. In any case, it&amp;#8217;s even easier to play Team Fortress Classic on Android. This is all thanks to an app called SDLash3D which uses the SDL library that allows you to do some really cool emulation such as running Windows 95 on your device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Android on Old PC</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-android-on-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 14:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-android-on-pc/</guid>
      <description>Do you have an old computer just sitting around? If you are like me, then you probably have a couple of old PC&amp;#8217;s that once ran Windows XP but serve no useful purpose now. Of course, I could always just install and very lite version of Linux on it and call it a day. However, Linux takes a lot of time (compared to Windows) to set up and is a big learning curve for people who are unfamiliar with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Phone From Android Wear</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-phone-from-android-wear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 14:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-phone-from-android-wear/</guid>
      <description>Security means everything to me. I am that guy who uses two step authentication on everything, along with safety backups and more. When it comes to security on Android, things aren&amp;#8217;t as tight as I would like them to be. On my S6, my favorite thing to use is the fingerprint scanner. I am aware that the fingerprint scanner does not offer better security than a strong password or lock pattern (although you could easily bypass the Android Lockscreen pattern), however, it will deter most people from trying to snoop around in my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coolest Apps Android wear 2015</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/coolest-apps-android-wear-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 14:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/coolest-apps-android-wear-2015/</guid>
      <description>I love trying out new things with my smartwatch. Here is a video featuring the coolest Android wear apps 2015. If apps aren&amp;#8217;t your thing, no problem. Check out my video on the Top Android wear games for your device.
PixToCam  Video for Android Wear Wear Audio recorder Web Browser for Android wear Staylit Wear Have any other cool apps? Feel free to share below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play PS2 Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-ps2-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 20:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-ps2-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>I am not lying when I tell you that there is an actual PS2 emulator available for Android. No, I am not talking about one of the many fake ones that you see in the Play Store. I am talking about an actual app with the purpose of emulating the PlayStation 2. Now don&amp;#8217;t get too excited. This app is still in the very early stages. The only commercial title that I have got booting so far has been Final Fantasy X.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Steam Games to Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-to-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 13:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-to-android/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to play Team Fortress or PlanetSide 2 on your Android device? Well, there is no way to do that, unless you&amp;#8217;re looking to play Team Fortress Classic on your Android device. However, you could stream these games from your computer to your Android device.
Currently, the most popular method used to stream games to Android is some combination of limelight and Nvidia&amp;#8217;s Game Stream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Runescape on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-runescape-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2015 23:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-runescape-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Back in fourth grade, I used to spend hours playing Runescape. At the time, I thought it was the most exciting and adventurous game out there. However, it&amp;#8217;s been about nine years since I have last played the game, so I am very behind on the latest additions and enhancements. In any case, if you are an active player, you will be happy to know that you can play this on your Chromebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Sega Genesis Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-sega-genesis-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 03:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-sega-genesis-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>The Sega Genesis was my very first game console. What my gaming PC is to me now, was what my Sega Genesis meant to me back in 1999 (if that makes sense). There are so many old titles that I used to love playing. And those cartridges&amp;#8230;damn&amp;#8230;I loved those cartridges. The best thing was that there used to be a huge bin at stores like GameStop, where I could easily pick up a bunch of them for under $10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Dreamcast Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-dreamcast-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 03:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-dreamcast-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>Ah, the Sega Dreamcast, it brings back old memories. Who am I kidding, I never had the Dreamcast myself. So unfortunately, my personal experience is limited to the only game (Sonic Adventures) that I have ever played on it. But, what I do know is that you can play Dreamcast games on Android!
What You Will Need:  Reicast or use This One if you are running a Lollipop Device and Experience Crashes with the Play Store version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Fun Facts About Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/6-fun-facts-about-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 23:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/6-fun-facts-about-android/</guid>
      <description>Android is full of surprises! Even when you think you know everything something new gets discovered. While you might be up to date with all the latest information, I am going to attempt to astonish you with 6 fun facts about android that you probably didn&amp;#8217;t know.
1. The Android Logo used to be scary We all know that Bugdroid is the official Android logo. However, before Android was officially launched, dandroid was the temporary logo used to represent the operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LG G4 Quick Review</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-quick-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 02:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-quick-review/</guid>
      <description>tl;dr
The LG G4 is seriously one of the best Android smartphones of 2015. It might not have the most attractive design on the outside and in the UI, but it is very responsive and can last you through a whole day with moderate-heavy usage.
The LG G4 Quick Review: Here is a quick review of the LG G4.
Screen: The LG G4 has a 2560x1440p display. LG calls it a quantum HD display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Play PS2 Games on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-ps2-games-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 03:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-ps2-games-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>I always said to never underestimate the power of Chromebooks, and here is another reason not to. You can play play PlayStation 2 Games on your Chromebook. In order to do this, you will need to have Linux** installed on your Chromebook. **We are going to use the popular PCSX2 emulator for Linux. So it&amp;#8217;s also important that you have an Intel powered chromebook.
Now, one word of advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LG G4 Gaming Performance</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-gaming-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 15:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-gaming-performance/</guid>
      <description>LG G4 Gaming Performance: Here is a quick look at the LG G4 gaming performance. If you are worried with LG&amp;#8217;s decision to use the Snapdragon 808 over the Snapdragon 810, don&amp;#8217;t be. In my testing, I used graphics heavy games such as GTA Vice City and Goat Simulator along with Real Racing 3. I could not get the device to lag, even with all the in game settings set to the max.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows XP on Android Wear Smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/windows-xp-on-android-wear-smartwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/windows-xp-on-android-wear-smartwatch/</guid>
      <description>Alan Turing, the great father of computer science, had once said that, &amp;#8220;Machines take me by surprise with great frequency.&amp;#8221; I think we could all relate to that statement in one way or another. From the age of early gaming, to the development of PDA&amp;#8217;s, Smartphones, Smartwatches and even Smart Glasses, there never seems to be a point where technology fails to impress us. What is even more astonishing is how outdated technology can easily become to us within a small amount of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Minecraft Server on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-minecraft-server-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 04:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-minecraft-server-on-android/</guid>
      <description>Here is how you can run Minecraft server on your Android device. This will allow anyone playing Minecraft on the desktop to connect to the server running on your device. To do this, you will first need to install Linux to your Android device then install java and run the Minecraft server jar file. It is actually a fairly easy process and takes no more than 15 minutes altogether.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Your Own Personal Cloud Server</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/create-your-own-personal-cloud-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 20:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/create-your-own-personal-cloud-server/</guid>
      <description>Whether it is Dropbox, Google Drive, Skydrive or iCloud, I am sure that we all have our favorite cloud server. Cloud Servers are great because they allow us to easily sync files between all the devices on our network and access content from anywhere. However, a growing concern over cloud servers is privacy. You could be banned from hosting certain content and companies could easily sort through what you are uploading and create targeted ads based on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy S6 Slow Motion Video</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s6-slow-motion-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 16:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s6-slow-motion-video/</guid>
      <description>Slow Motion seems to be all the rage these days. Every one is trying to do it. It should come as no surprise that the Galaxy S6 also features this. While the Galaxy S6 slow motion video capabilities don&amp;#8217;t exactly rival those of the iPhone, it&amp;#8217;s still pretty good in its own right. In this video, I use the built in slow motion editor. Of course, a much better way would have been to record the video in 60fps then slow it down in Adobe Premiere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Ubuntu 14.04 on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-ubuntu-14-04-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2015 03:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-ubuntu-14-04-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>I am always looking for different ways that I can extend the capability of my Chromebook. It&amp;#8217;s not that I don&amp;#8217;t like Chrome OS, but sometimes I need to launch a C compiler or run java apps when I am away from home. I might even get in the mood to play Minecraft during a long car ride. Luckily, there is an easy answer to all of this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counter Strike Global Offensive on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/counter-strike-global-offensive-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 15:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/counter-strike-global-offensive-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Counter Strike Global Offensive on Chromebook? Are you tired of playing the same old games on your Chromebook? Well, with a little help from Linux and Steam you can play CS:Go on your Chromebook. Of course, this will only work with the Intel powered Chromebooks. As far as performance, it&amp;#8217;s playable. On average, I am getting around 23-30 fps in games. It&amp;#8217;s nowhere close to the performance that I get on my desktop, but is still playable none the less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable Developer mode on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/enable-developer-mode-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2015 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/enable-developer-mode-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to install Linux on your Chromebook or Windows 10? If so, the first thing that you will need to do is enable developer mode on your Chromebook. Also, these instructions could differ depending on your Chromebook model. For this tutorial, I am going to be using the Acer C720.
Enable Developer Mode on Chromebook: This process will erase everything on your Chromebook. So backup anything that you might need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Windows 10 on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-windows-10-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 19:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-windows-10-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>So let&amp;#8217;s say that you bought a Chromebook and realized just how limiting Chrome OS can be, or perhaps you are perfectly content with Chrome OS but want to do a little more with it. Whatever your situation may be, I am here to inform you that you can run Windows 10 on your Chromebook. Yes, I am talking about a complete and nearly functional version of Windows 10. In my quick time of using it, I was able to download and play League of Legends (unbearable frame rate though) watch a couple of YouTube videos and use a few lightweight programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/windows-10-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 20:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/windows-10-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Yes, you can run Windows 10 on a Chromebook! Now this should not come as too much of a surprise because Chromebooks are pretty much low powered laptops with Chrome OS installed. In addition, Windows 10 is designed to work with devices with lower end specifications. Overall, the performance was fluid. Between browsing through the start menu and opening up Internet Explorer, I did not encounter any issues.
There are some technical things to mention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would you only buy a Galaxy or iPhone?</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/would-you-only-buy-a-galaxy-or-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 05:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/would-you-only-buy-a-galaxy-or-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Would you only buy a Galaxy or iPhone?   So the other day, I was chatting with my friend about new smartphones. He currently owns the Galaxy S5 and was thinking about either upgrading to the Galaxy S6 or the iPhone. I jokingly informed him that there are other Android smartphone manufacturers such as HTC, LG, Motorola, etc. However he told me, &amp;#8220;Dave, honestly, unless it&amp;#8217;s a Galaxy or iPhone, I wouldn&amp;#8217;t consider buying it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play PSP Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-psp-games-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 19:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-psp-games-android/</guid>
      <description>Play PSP Games on Android Yes, you can play PSP games on your Android device. This is not a gimmick, nor some sort of absurd remote VNC. This is pure emulation right on your Android device. It is all thanks to the app PPSSPP. Surprisingly, some games work with excellent frame rate and graphics quality (Naruto for example). Keep in mind though, not every game will be compatible and it will not work with every device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Python on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-python-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 19:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-python-android/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to program on your phone? Well, believe it or not, you can craft code right in the palm of your hands. Python is not only a flexible programming language, it is also capable of running on your Android phone thanks to the app QPython3.
Run Python on Android What You&amp;#8217;ll Need:  QPython3  With QPython3 you have access you to a multitude of tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Portal on any Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-portal-on-any-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 19:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-portal-on-any-android/</guid>
      <description>Ah yes, who doesn&amp;#8217;t love a good game of Portal? If you are lucky enough to own an Nvidia Shield (or any Tegra 4 device), you already have access to the game plus more exclusives. But what if you do not own an Nvidia Shield? Well there is still a way to play Portal thanks to an app called GLTools. GLtTools will emulate the Tegra 4 drivers, so that the app thinks you are using a Tegra 4 device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bypass Android Lock screen</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/bypass-android-lock-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 04:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/bypass-android-lock-screen/</guid>
      <description>Locked out of your phone? Well you are in luck. There is a way to bypass your Android lock screen. Now before you get too excited, there are a few stipulations. First, this only works when your security is set to pattern lock. Secondly, you must have a rooted android device. And finally, you need to have adb debugging enabled. I know this might only be a small percentage of people out there, so for those of you who do, here&amp;#8217;s how you can bypass Android lock screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Flash Player Android Lollipop</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/adobe-flash-player-android-lollipop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 05:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/adobe-flash-player-android-lollipop/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Flash Player Android Lollipop: At one time, Android fully supported adobe flash player. However, official support ended by the time KitKat was released (though there were still a few hacks that you could use to get it). Of course, HTML5 video players are the preferred option, but unfortunately, there are some porn sites that still rely heavily on adobe flash content.
&amp;nbsp;
Well, if you have an Android device running Lollipop you can now access the flash content once more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tor for Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tor-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 05:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tor-android/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s talk about internet privacy. So as you might be aware of, when you open up a tab in incognito mode you&amp;#8217;re not really browsing anonymously. Your ISP and and any one else who is monitoring your internet can get your location and see the sites you visited. To truly browse the internet privately, you need to use tor.
To keep it brief, Tor is a mesh of proxy servers that bounces your IP to different locations across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boot Computer from Android Phone</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/boot-computer-from-android-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 02:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/boot-computer-from-android-phone/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself in a situation where you didn&amp;#8217;t have a flash drive handy? Well, the other day I was trying to re-install Windows on my laptop, and sure enough, my USB flash drive conveniently went missing. Luckily, I was able to use my Nexus 5 to mount the ISO and boot my laptop from it. So here&amp;#8217;s how you can boot computer from Android phone:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Android apps on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-android-apps-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 22:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-android-apps-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Recently, Google has released an Android run-time for Chrome OS that will allow developers to easily port their android applications to Chrome OS (Feel free to watch the Keynote for more information). While this is a step in the right direction (and should have been included with Chrome OS from the very beginning, but I digress) there are only four official android apps available for Chrome OS (Evernote, Vine, Sight Words, Duolingo).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Paranoid Android Features</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-paranoid-android-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 17:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-paranoid-android-features/</guid>
      <description>Paranoid Android is by far one of my favorite custom roms.. It provides a stock like experience with added functionality. Each month the PA team has added a new signature feature to this amazing rom. So here&amp;#8217;s a look at some of the best paranoid android features.
Dynamic System Bars:   The newest feature found on Paranoid Android is Dynamic System bars. DSB allows you to tint your status and navigation bars to the color of the foreground app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Android on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-android-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 05:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-android-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of Chrome OS? Do you want a greater selection of apps and games? Well, running Android on your Chromebook is a practical option. The performance is without compromise and almost everything works (except for the touchpad). You will have access to the entire Google Play store so you can download games and thousands of apps. So here&amp;#8217;s how to run Android on Chromebook.
What You Will Need:  An Intel Powered Chromebook A USB with at least 2GB of free space Android X86 iSO Rufus  Step 1: Developer Mode Before you can run Android, you will need to put your Chromebook in developer mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Lock Screen Notifications</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-lock-screen-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 22:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-lock-screen-notifications/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#8217;re looking for a way to get notifications on your lock screen, then check out this video: Android Lock Screen Notifications. Using an app called echo Lockscreen, you can get notifications on your device&amp;#8217;s lock screen. It also turns on your screen when you get a notification such as a text message; I think that&amp;#8217;s one of the major advantages to this app. Give it a try and tell me what you think about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disable Lock screen at Home</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/disable-lock-screen-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 15:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/disable-lock-screen-at-home/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s face it, at home, there might not be a huge risk to leaving your phone unlocked. Yes, a sibling could snoop into your phone and take a look at those risque pictures you have saved or see who you have been texting, but that might not be the absolute worst security breach to deal with. Luckily, Android Lollipop adds a trusted device feature that allows you to automatically disable your lock screen if you are on a trusted wifi network or connected to a trusted Bluetooth device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows XP on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/windows-xp-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2014 13:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/windows-xp-android/</guid>
      <description>Yes Virginia, you can run Windows XP on your Android device. What once took cutting edge hardware to boot, can now work on your typical Android smartphone. Don&amp;#8217;t get too excited though, this will not replace your desktop pc any time soon. The emulation speed is unbearably slow, and you lack any sort of network connectivity. So how does this work? One word, Bochs. Bochs is an app that can emulate practically any 32 bit operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Windows 95 on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-windows-95-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 20:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-windows-95-on-android/</guid>
      <description>The 90s called, and they want their operating system back. Windows 95 was unique for its time. However, what once took cutting edge hardware to run can now easily operate on a typical Android device. Yes Virginia, you can run Windows 95 on Android.
What You Will Need:  Windows 95 Image File Limbo PC Emulator  Step 1: Download Stuff If you have your own bootable image file that you would like to use, feel free to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Windows 8 on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-windows-8-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 17:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/install-windows-8-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Windows 8 is old news now, look at running Windows 10 on your Chromebook! So you want to run Windows 8 on your Chromebook? Well congratulations, you clicked on the right link. Let me first ask you a question. Are you looking for a fully responsive, practical and reliable Windows 8 chromebook system? If so, then go out and buy a Windows netbook. While running Windows 8 on your Chromebook is feasible, there are a lot of driver hurdles and hardware limitations (depending on your Chromebook model) that you will have to overcome before this becomes a practical solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Ubuntu on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/intsall-ubuntu-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 15:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/intsall-ubuntu-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has their own opinion of Chrome OS. Some find it extremely useful and others think it&amp;#8217;s complete garbage. While I would consider myself part of the former group, I can admit that there are places where Chrome OS falls short of a desktop operating system. For exampling, I&amp;#8217;m not able to open a java compiler on Chrome OS or use Wine to play Steam games. However, you can do all these things on Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Root Any Android Device</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-root-any-android-device-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-root-any-android-device-2014/</guid>
      <description>There are some things in life that sound too good to be true. However, this isn&amp;#8217;t one of them. George Hortz, a hacker made famous by his iOS jailbreaks and PlayStation hacks has managed to root the Verizon Galaxy S5. So why should you care? Well, he used a recently discovered exploit found in all Linux kernels that were built prior to June 3rd. So in theory (and in practice) his app should work on any Android device that has a kernel build date prior to June 3rd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/share-computer-internet-connection-with-android-reverse-tethering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 23:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/share-computer-internet-connection-with-android-reverse-tethering/</guid>
      <description>Everyone is familiar with tethering. However, many people overlook the ability to reverse tether. Reverse tethering allows you to share your computer&amp;#8217;s internet connection with your phone or tablet. This is useful if you&amp;#8217;re on a metered data plan or in an area which has no wifi and a weak mobile signal. 
What You Will Need:  A rooted Android Device A Windows PC USB Driver Reverse Tether Zip (Go to this thread to download or direct download here)  Step 1: Install USB Drivers If you don&amp;#8217;t have any device drivers already installed on your computer and you never used adb before, then you will need to install the USB drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Ubuntu 13.10 on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-ubuntu-13-10-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 15:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-ubuntu-13-10-on-android/</guid>
      <description>How would it feel to have the power of a desktop operating system in the palm of your hands? If you&amp;#8217;re a power user, and also a fan of Linux, then you came to the right place. Running Ubuntu 13.10 on your Android device is not very hard to do. Don&amp;#8217;t think that this is some slow or stripped down version of Ubuntu. You will have access to all your favorite Linux apps and commands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build Custom Cyanogenmod Rom</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-custom-cyanogenmod-rom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 08:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-build-custom-cyanogenmod-rom/</guid>
      <description>Build Custom Cyanogenmod Rom? So are you ready to take on Rom Development? That&amp;#8217;s okay if you&amp;#8217;re not, because I&amp;#8217;ll help walk you through it. In this tutorial, I&amp;#8217;m going to show you how to build your own Cyanogenmod Rom right from source. This sounds a lot more complicated than it actually is though. However, keep in mind that you will need a lot of patience when doing this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable Ultra High Graphics Dead Trigger 2</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/enable-ultra-high-graphics-dead-trigger-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/enable-ultra-high-graphics-dead-trigger-2/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s not surprising that certain games purposefully limit the maximum graphics level that the user could set. However, it becomes an issue when the device you&amp;#8217;re playing on is more than capable of handling the maximum graphics level, even though the developers didn&amp;#8217;t think so. Unfortunately, Dead Trigger 2 is a perfect example of this scenario. Fortunately, with a little file modification you can enable the secret &amp;#8220;ultra&amp;#8221; graphics mode only accessible to latest generation iPhones and Tegra devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Xposed Framework</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-xposed-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 14:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-xposed-framework/</guid>
      <description>Xposed is a popular framework that allows you to modify and customize your Android device without having to flash a new rom. It allows you to use a variety of apps and tools (such as gravity box) that extend what you can achieve with your Android device. If you&amp;#8217;re tinkerer or someone who thrives on complete control, than Xposed it what you want. For more techinical details on Xposed read this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Boost Speaker Volume</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-boost-speaker-volume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 04:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-boost-speaker-volume/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s face it. Even at max volume, sometimes the speaker on your phone just isn&amp;#8217;t loud enough (Yes, I&amp;#8217;m looking at you Nexus 5). However, you could digitally raise the maximum volume that the speaker allows itself to go to. This will require a rooted android device and could run the risk of damaging your speakers if you go too high, so be warned.
What You will Need:  A rooted Android Device ES File Explorer  Step 1: Mounting the System Open up ES file explorer and enable the root explorer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Play Nintendo DS Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-nintendo-ds-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 15:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-nintendo-ds-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>The Nintendo DS was by far one of my favorite portable game systems. However, these were the days before smartphone gaming became the norm. If you&amp;#8217;re feeling nostalgic and in the mood to play some DS games on your Android device, it&amp;#8217;s very easy thanks to the DraStic DS emulator. Here&amp;#8217;s how to play Nintendo DS games on Android:
What You&amp;#8217;ll Need:  A Nintendo Game (nds Rom)(You can Google it) DraStic DS Emulator (Demo) DraStic DS Emulator (Full)  Step 1: Transferring the Rom to Your Device The first thing you need to do is transfer the Rom to your device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Floating Window</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-floating-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 04:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-floating-window/</guid>
      <description>One of the most iconic features of the Galaxy Note 3, is the multi-window feature. It&amp;#8217;s extremely cool and makes great use of the abundance of screen real estate. Unfortunately, that&amp;#8217;s not a native Android feature. However, with the help of an Xposed Module, you can achieve the floating affect on any android device. Here&amp;#8217;s how to get Android floating window display:
What You Will Need:  A rooted Android Device Xposed Installer App Halo App(Android 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play PlayStation Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-playstation-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 03:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/play-playstation-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>Do you miss the good old PlayStation days? I am talking about the original PlayStation with the 1MB Memory cards (I had a lot of those) and the boring yet simplistic outer-body design? If so, there is hope for you. Thanks to multiple apps in the Play Store, you can play PlayStation games on Android.
Emulation has come so far on Android. It amazes me at just how many titles are compatible with the PlayStation emulators.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>