<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Best on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/best/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Best on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:12:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/best/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Extensions for Google Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-extensions-google-chrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-extensions-google-chrome/</guid>
      <description>The best thing about Google Chrome is all the extensions that are available for it. Now I recently learned that Microsoft Edge also has extensions, but nowhere near as many as google chrome. By no means is this an exhaustive list of all the best extensions for Google Chrome; just a few of my favorites that I use every day.
Ghostery 
If you are concerned about your privacy on the internet, then Ghostery is the perfect app for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s on my Phone</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/whats-on-my-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 14:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/whats-on-my-phone/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;#8217;s on my phone? I want to share with you some of the Android apps that I use on my phone everyday.
Android Customization:  Nova Launcher Iride UI is Hipster Zooper Widget Zooper Widget Theme  Productivity:  Google Keep Todoist Inbox Evernote Calendar Widget  Texting:  Textra  Social:  Buffer Fenix Sync for Reddit  &amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Paranoid Android Features</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-paranoid-android-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 17:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/best-paranoid-android-features/</guid>
      <description>Paranoid Android is by far one of my favorite custom roms.. It provides a stock like experience with added functionality. Each month the PA team has added a new signature feature to this amazing rom. So here&amp;#8217;s a look at some of the best paranoid android features.
Dynamic System Bars:   The newest feature found on Paranoid Android is Dynamic System bars. DSB allows you to tint your status and navigation bars to the color of the foreground app.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>