<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Opensourcegangster on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://bennettnotes.com/tags/opensourcegangster/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Opensourcegangster on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 15:59:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bennettnotes.com/tags/opensourcegangster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Android cSploit</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/android-csploit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 15:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/android-csploit-2/</guid>
      <description>A little while ago, there was this awesome program called dSploit. It was a network security app that provided users with an abundance of tools and operations to test the strength of their network security. Recently, dSploit was merged with a proprietary closed source app that isn&amp;#8217;t free. While you can find older copies of dSploit floating around on the internet, none of them are up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android cSploit</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/android-csploit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 15:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/android-csploit/</guid>
      <description>A little while ago, there was this awesome program called dSploit. It was a network security app that provided users with an abundance of tools and operations to test the strength of their network security. Recently, dSploit was merged with a proprietary closed source app that isn&amp;#8217;t free. While you can find older copies of dSploit floating around on the internet, none of them are up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Windows 95 on Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/run-windows-95-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 20:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/run-windows-95-on-android/</guid>
      <description>The 90s called, and they want their operating system back. Windows 95 was unique for its time. However, what once took cutting edge hardware to run can now easily operate on a typical Android device. Yes Virginia, you can run Windows 95 on Android.
What You Will Need:  Windows 95 Image File Limbo PC Emulator  Step 1: Download Stuff If you have your own bootable image file that you would like to use, feel free to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Windows 8 on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/install-windows-8-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 17:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/install-windows-8-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Windows 8 is old news now, look at running Windows 10 on your Chromebook! So you want to run Windows 8 on your Chromebook? Well congratulations, you clicked on the right link. Let me first ask you a question. Are you looking for a fully responsive, practical and reliable Windows 8 chromebook system? If so, then go out and buy a Windows netbook. While running Windows 8 on your Chromebook is feasible, there are a lot of driver hurdles and hardware limitations (depending on your Chromebook model) that you will have to overcome before this becomes a practical solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Ubuntu on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/intsall-ubuntu-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 15:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/intsall-ubuntu-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has their own opinion of Chrome OS. Some find it extremely useful and others think it&amp;#8217;s complete garbage. While I would consider myself part of the former group, I can admit that there are places where Chrome OS falls short of a desktop operating system. For exampling, I&amp;#8217;m not able to open a java compiler on Chrome OS or use Wine to play Steam games. However, you can do all these things on Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Ubuntu 13.10 on Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/run-ubuntu-13-10-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 15:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/run-ubuntu-13-10-on-android/</guid>
      <description>How would it feel to have the power of a desktop operating system in the palm of your hands? If you&amp;#8217;re a power user, and also a fan of Linux, then you came to the right place. Running Ubuntu 13.10 on your Android device is not very hard to do. Don&amp;#8217;t think that this is some slow or stripped down version of Ubuntu. You will have access to all your favorite Linux apps and commands.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>