<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows 10 on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://bennettnotes.com/tags/windows-10/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows 10 on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 15:41:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bennettnotes.com/tags/windows-10/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove Bloatware from Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-remove-bloatware-from-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 15:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-remove-bloatware-from-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>Believe it or not, Windows 10 comes with a lot of bloatware pre-installed on it. Things like Candy crash, Bing Weather, Bing Sports, etc. If you really wanted to, you could go through the programs and features tool and remove each app individually. However, that would take a lot of unnecessary time and some apps wouldn&amp;#8217;t show up in that menu. To overcome this challenge, a user on GitHub created a Windows 10 bloatware removal script that uses PowerShell to remove the unnecessary apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dual Boot Windows 10 and Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/dual-boot-windows-10-and-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 02:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/dual-boot-windows-10-and-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>I woke up Sunday Morning with a cool project in mind. I wanted to dual boot Windows 10 and Ubuntu. The real reason for this was because I decided to give Jekyll a try and it was going to be my replacement for WordPress, but I digress. Another major reason to dual-boot Windows 10 and Ubuntu was so that I could keep all of my Android development and Web development stuff within Ubuntu and use Windows solely for video editing and gaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replace Chrome OS with Windows</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/replace-chrome-os-with-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 22:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/replace-chrome-os-with-windows/</guid>
      <description>I love Chrome OS but I also realize that it&amp;#8217;s pretty useless without an internet connection. Okay&amp;#8230;maybe not pretty useless but _mostly useless._ I can&amp;#8217;t game, program or do anything useful on Chrome OS other than browse the web. Luckily, if you are using a Chromebook with an Intel CPU (sorry Samsung Chromebook users) you can replace Chrome OS with Windows. Previously, I did a tutorial on How to install Windows on a Chromebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux in Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/linux-in-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/linux-in-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has done something really cool in the Windows 10 Anniversary Update. They gave users the ability to use the Linux Bash Command Line from within Windows. This is not through a virtual machine nor container, but a subsystem that they previously added in an earlier Windows update. Here&amp;#8217;s how you can enable Linux in Windows 10:
What You Will Need:  Windows 10 Anniversary Update  How To: ­</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Windows 10 on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/install-windows-10-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 19:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/install-windows-10-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>So let&amp;#8217;s say that you bought a Chromebook and realized just how limiting Chrome OS can be, or perhaps you are perfectly content with Chrome OS but want to do a little more with it. Whatever your situation may be, I am here to inform you that you can run Windows 10 on your Chromebook. Yes, I am talking about a complete and nearly functional version of Windows 10. In my quick time of using it, I was able to download and play League of Legends (unbearable frame rate though) watch a couple of YouTube videos and use a few lightweight programs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>