<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Games on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://bennettnotes.com/tags/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 15:00:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bennettnotes.com/tags/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Play PlayStation 3 Games on PC</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/play-playstation-3-games-on-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/play-playstation-3-games-on-pc/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube JrIdxHpAUm8 {}
Although the PlayStation 4 is the latest console from Sony, the PlayStation 3 is still a popular game system that is enjoyed by many. One group of developers have been actively working to bring the PlayStation 3 experience to your PC. RPCS3 is an open source PlayStation 3 emulator. The emulator is still in early alpha stages, so don&amp;#8217;t expect many commercial titles to be compatible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack Android Apps and Games</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/hack-android-apps-and-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 14:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/hack-android-apps-and-games/</guid>
      <description>Wouldn&amp;#8217;t it be great if every game had cheat codes? Well, this might be closer than you think. Using the app Game Guardian, we can change the value of any numerical data within Android games. Yes, you can now achieve an unbeatable high score in your favorite game.
To do this you will need to have a rooted Android device. The process for this is fairly simple. We need to find the location of the desired attribute then change its value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play PS2 Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/play-ps2-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 20:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/play-ps2-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>I am not lying when I tell you that there is an actual PS2 emulator available for Android. No, I am not talking about one of the many fake ones that you see in the Play Store. I am talking about an actual app with the purpose of emulating the PlayStation 2. Now don&amp;#8217;t get too excited. This app is still in the very early stages. The only commercial title that I have got booting so far has been Final Fantasy X.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Steam Games to Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-to-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 13:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-to-android/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube BmjMOCTU6YA {}
Have you ever wanted to play Team Fortress or PlanetSide 2 on your Android device? Well, there is no way to do that, unless you&amp;#8217;re looking to play Team Fortress Classic on your Android device. However, you could stream these games from your computer to your Android device.
[adinserter block=&amp;#8221;5&amp;#8243;]
Currently, the most popular method used to stream games to Android is some combination of limelight and Nvidia&amp;#8217;s Game Stream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Sega Genesis Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/play-sega-genesis-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 03:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/play-sega-genesis-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>The Sega Genesis was my very first game console. What my gaming PC is to me now, was what my Sega Genesis meant to me back in 1999 (if that makes sense). There are so many old titles that I used to love playing. And those cartridges&amp;#8230;damn&amp;#8230;I loved those cartridges. The best thing was that there used to be a huge bin at stores like GameStop, where I could easily pick up a bunch of them for under $10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Dreamcast Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/play-dreamcast-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 03:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/play-dreamcast-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>Ah, the Sega Dreamcast, it brings back old memories. Who am I kidding, I never had the Dreamcast myself. So unfortunately, my personal experience is limited to the only game (Sonic Adventures) that I have ever played on it. But, what I do know is that you can play Dreamcast games on Android!
What You Will Need:  Reicast or use This One if you are running a Lollipop Device and Experience Crashes with the Play Store version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Play PS2 Games on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-ps2-games-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 03:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-ps2-games-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube WbiInD2oB5I {}
I always said to never underestimate the power of Chromebooks, and here is another reason not to. You can play play PlayStation 2 Games on your Chromebook. In order to do this, you will need to have Linux** installed on your Chromebook. **We are going to use the popular PCSX2 emulator for Linux. So it&amp;#8217;s also important that you have an Intel powered chromebook.
[adinserter block=&amp;#8221;5&amp;#8243;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play PSP Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/play-psp-games-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 19:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/play-psp-games-android/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube d9NxlMTDi88 {}
Play PSP Games on Android Yes, you can play PSP games on your Android device. This is not a gimmick, nor some sort of absurd remote VNC. This is pure emulation right on your Android device. It is all thanks to the app PPSSPP. Surprisingly, some games work with excellent frame rate and graphics quality (Naruto for example). Keep in mind though, not every game will be compatible and it will not work with every device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Android apps on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/run-android-apps-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 22:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/run-android-apps-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube nx8vIAjUNmo {}
Recently, Google has released an Android run-time for Chrome OS that will allow developers to easily port their android applications to Chrome OS (Feel free to watch the Keynote for more information). While this is a step in the right direction (and should have been included with Chrome OS from the very beginning, but I digress) there are only four official android apps available for Chrome OS (Evernote, Vine, Sight Words, Duolingo).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Play Nintendo DS Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-nintendo-ds-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 15:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-nintendo-ds-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>The Nintendo DS was by far one of my favorite portable game systems. However, these were the days before smartphone gaming became the norm. If you&amp;#8217;re feeling nostalgic and in the mood to play some DS games on your Android device, it&amp;#8217;s very easy thanks to the DraStic DS emulator. Here&amp;#8217;s how to play Nintendo DS games on Android:
What You&amp;#8217;ll Need:  A Nintendo Game (nds Rom)(You can Google it) DraStic DS Emulator (Demo) DraStic DS Emulator (Full)  Step 1: Transferring the Rom to Your Device The first thing you need to do is transfer the Rom to your device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play PlayStation Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/play-playstation-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 03:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/play-playstation-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube UA9WCJO6X44 {}
Do you miss the good old PlayStation days? I am talking about the original PlayStation with the 1MB Memory cards (I had a lot of those) and the boring yet simplistic outer-body design? If so, there is hope for you. Thanks to multiple apps in the Play Store, you can play PlayStation games on Android.
[adinserter block=&amp;#8221;5&amp;#8243;]
Emulation has come so far on Android. It amazes me at just how many titles are compatible with the PlayStation emulators.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>