<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Install on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://bennettnotes.com/tags/install/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Install on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 22:02:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bennettnotes.com/tags/install/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Linux</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-linux/</guid>
      <description>Now that you are familiar with Linux, how do you go about installing it? Well, the beauty of Linux is that there are many different flavors at your disposal, in the form of distributions. Each distribution offers its own pre-installed software and default desktop and environment. There are thousands of different Linux distributions to choose from. If you are looking for a distribution that fits your needs, check out this list of the top 11 best Linux distributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Chrome OS on PC</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-chrome-os-on-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 02:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-chrome-os-on-pc/</guid>
      <description>I recently came to the realization that Chrome OS is in some ways a perfect operating system. No, I swear I&amp;#8217;m not taking any hallucinogens. Here is a scenario that really opened my mind. I have an aunt who uses a basic low spec PC running Windows XP. All she does is check her email and check Facebook once per day, and that&amp;#8217;s it. Unfortunately, her PC barely meets the requirements to run Windows XP effectively and is constantly cluttered from maleware, Trojans, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Mac OS X Yosemite on any PC</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-mac-os-x-yosemite-on-any-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 01:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-mac-os-x-yosemite-on-any-pc/</guid>
      <description>I will be the first to admit that I prefer Windows over Mac OS any day. Besides being a slight Microsoft fanboy, I do prefer Windows because it meets all of my software and gaming needs, but I digress. In any case, there are still some unfortunate situations when I need to have access to Mac OS.
[adinserter block=&amp;#8221;5&amp;#8243;]
Luckily, I&amp;#8217;ll show you an easy way on how to install Mac OS X Yosemite on any pc, regardless of the hardware that you currently have installed (even if it is an AMD CPU).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Android on Old PC</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/install-android-on-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 14:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/install-android-on-pc/</guid>
      <description>Do you have an old computer just sitting around? If you are like me, then you probably have a couple of old PC&amp;#8217;s that once ran Windows XP but serve no useful purpose now. Of course, I could always just install and very lite version of Linux on it and call it a day. However, Linux takes a lot of time (compared to Windows) to set up and is a big learning curve for people who are unfamiliar with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Windows 10 on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/install-windows-10-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 19:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/install-windows-10-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>So let&amp;#8217;s say that you bought a Chromebook and realized just how limiting Chrome OS can be, or perhaps you are perfectly content with Chrome OS but want to do a little more with it. Whatever your situation may be, I am here to inform you that you can run Windows 10 on your Chromebook. Yes, I am talking about a complete and nearly functional version of Windows 10. In my quick time of using it, I was able to download and play League of Legends (unbearable frame rate though) watch a couple of YouTube videos and use a few lightweight programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Flash Player Android Lollipop</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/adobe-flash-player-android-lollipop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 05:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/adobe-flash-player-android-lollipop/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Flash Player Android Lollipop: At one time, Android fully supported adobe flash player. However, official support ended by the time KitKat was released (though there were still a few hacks that you could use to get it). Of course, HTML5 video players are the preferred option, but unfortunately, there are some porn sites that still rely heavily on adobe flash content.
[adinserter block=&amp;#8221;5&amp;#8243;]
&amp;nbsp;
Well, if you have an Android device running Lollipop you can now access the flash content once more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Windows 8 on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/install-windows-8-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 17:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/install-windows-8-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Windows 8 is old news now, look at running Windows 10 on your Chromebook! So you want to run Windows 8 on your Chromebook? Well congratulations, you clicked on the right link. Let me first ask you a question. Are you looking for a fully responsive, practical and reliable Windows 8 chromebook system? If so, then go out and buy a Windows netbook. While running Windows 8 on your Chromebook is feasible, there are a lot of driver hurdles and hardware limitations (depending on your Chromebook model) that you will have to overcome before this becomes a practical solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Ubuntu on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/intsall-ubuntu-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 15:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/intsall-ubuntu-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has their own opinion of Chrome OS. Some find it extremely useful and others think it&amp;#8217;s complete garbage. While I would consider myself part of the former group, I can admit that there are places where Chrome OS falls short of a desktop operating system. For exampling, I&amp;#8217;m not able to open a java compiler on Chrome OS or use Wine to play Steam games. However, you can do all these things on Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Ubuntu 13.10 on Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/run-ubuntu-13-10-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 15:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/run-ubuntu-13-10-on-android/</guid>
      <description>How would it feel to have the power of a desktop operating system in the palm of your hands? If you&amp;#8217;re a power user, and also a fan of Linux, then you came to the right place. Running Ubuntu 13.10 on your Android device is not very hard to do. Don&amp;#8217;t think that this is some slow or stripped down version of Ubuntu. You will have access to all your favorite Linux apps and commands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Xposed Framework</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-xposed-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 14:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-xposed-framework/</guid>
      <description>Xposed is a popular framework that allows you to modify and customize your Android device without having to flash a new rom. It allows you to use a variety of apps and tools (such as gravity box) that extend what you can achieve with your Android device. If you&amp;#8217;re tinkerer or someone who thrives on complete control, than Xposed it what you want. For more techinical details on Xposed read this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>