<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>smartphone on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/smartphone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in smartphone on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 16:49:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/smartphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixel 3 Review – Don’t Romanticize Imperfection</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/pixel-3-review-dont-romanticize-imperfection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 16:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/pixel-3-review-dont-romanticize-imperfection/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s not romanticize imperfection. The Pixel 3 is not _The Little Engine That Could, _or some gifted boy who was born without legs. There are people out there who treat Google like the underdog; despite the fact that they have full control over the future of Android. And while there&amp;#8217;s nothing wrong with having favorites in a race, it can be dangerous to idolize a runner just based off his shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moto Z Play Review</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/moto-z-play-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 14:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/moto-z-play-review/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a phone that will give you the best battery life? If so, the $450 unlocked Moto Z Play is what you need. Check out this video of the Moto Z Play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LG G4 Quick Review</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-quick-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 02:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-quick-review/</guid>
      <description>tl;dr
The LG G4 is seriously one of the best Android smartphones of 2015. It might not have the most attractive design on the outside and in the UI, but it is very responsive and can last you through a whole day with moderate-heavy usage.
The LG G4 Quick Review: Here is a quick review of the LG G4.
Screen: The LG G4 has a 2560x1440p display. LG calls it a quantum HD display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LG G4 Gaming Performance</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-gaming-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 15:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-gaming-performance/</guid>
      <description>LG G4 Gaming Performance: Here is a quick look at the LG G4 gaming performance. If you are worried with LG&amp;#8217;s decision to use the Snapdragon 808 over the Snapdragon 810, don&amp;#8217;t be. In my testing, I used graphics heavy games such as GTA Vice City and Goat Simulator along with Real Racing 3. I could not get the device to lag, even with all the in game settings set to the max.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy S6 Slow Motion Video</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s6-slow-motion-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 16:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s6-slow-motion-video/</guid>
      <description>Slow Motion seems to be all the rage these days. Every one is trying to do it. It should come as no surprise that the Galaxy S6 also features this. While the Galaxy S6 slow motion video capabilities don&amp;#8217;t exactly rival those of the iPhone, it&amp;#8217;s still pretty good in its own right. In this video, I use the built in slow motion editor. Of course, a much better way would have been to record the video in 60fps then slow it down in Adobe Premiere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Python on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-python-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 19:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-python-android/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to program on your phone? Well, believe it or not, you can craft code right in the palm of your hands. Python is not only a flexible programming language, it is also capable of running on your Android phone thanks to the app QPython3.
Run Python on Android What You&amp;#8217;ll Need:  QPython3  With QPython3 you have access you to a multitude of tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tor for Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tor-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 05:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tor-android/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s talk about internet privacy. So as you might be aware of, when you open up a tab in incognito mode you&amp;#8217;re not really browsing anonymously. Your ISP and and any one else who is monitoring your internet can get your location and see the sites you visited. To truly browse the internet privately, you need to use tor.
To keep it brief, Tor is a mesh of proxy servers that bounces your IP to different locations across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Windows 95 on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-windows-95-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 20:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-windows-95-on-android/</guid>
      <description>The 90s called, and they want their operating system back. Windows 95 was unique for its time. However, what once took cutting edge hardware to run can now easily operate on a typical Android device. Yes Virginia, you can run Windows 95 on Android.
What You Will Need:  Windows 95 Image File Limbo PC Emulator  Step 1: Download Stuff If you have your own bootable image file that you would like to use, feel free to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Root Any Android Device</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-root-any-android-device-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-root-any-android-device-2014/</guid>
      <description>There are some things in life that sound too good to be true. However, this isn&amp;#8217;t one of them. George Hortz, a hacker made famous by his iOS jailbreaks and PlayStation hacks has managed to root the Verizon Galaxy S5. So why should you care? Well, he used a recently discovered exploit found in all Linux kernels that were built prior to June 3rd. So in theory (and in practice) his app should work on any Android device that has a kernel build date prior to June 3rd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/share-computer-internet-connection-with-android-reverse-tethering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 23:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/share-computer-internet-connection-with-android-reverse-tethering/</guid>
      <description>Everyone is familiar with tethering. However, many people overlook the ability to reverse tether. Reverse tethering allows you to share your computer&amp;#8217;s internet connection with your phone or tablet. This is useful if you&amp;#8217;re on a metered data plan or in an area which has no wifi and a weak mobile signal. 
What You Will Need:  A rooted Android Device A Windows PC USB Driver Reverse Tether Zip (Go to this thread to download or direct download here)  Step 1: Install USB Drivers If you don&amp;#8217;t have any device drivers already installed on your computer and you never used adb before, then you will need to install the USB drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Ubuntu 13.10 on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-ubuntu-13-10-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 15:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/run-ubuntu-13-10-on-android/</guid>
      <description>How would it feel to have the power of a desktop operating system in the palm of your hands? If you&amp;#8217;re a power user, and also a fan of Linux, then you came to the right place. Running Ubuntu 13.10 on your Android device is not very hard to do. Don&amp;#8217;t think that this is some slow or stripped down version of Ubuntu. You will have access to all your favorite Linux apps and commands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable Ultra High Graphics Dead Trigger 2</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/enable-ultra-high-graphics-dead-trigger-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/enable-ultra-high-graphics-dead-trigger-2/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s not surprising that certain games purposefully limit the maximum graphics level that the user could set. However, it becomes an issue when the device you&amp;#8217;re playing on is more than capable of handling the maximum graphics level, even though the developers didn&amp;#8217;t think so. Unfortunately, Dead Trigger 2 is a perfect example of this scenario. Fortunately, with a little file modification you can enable the secret &amp;#8220;ultra&amp;#8221; graphics mode only accessible to latest generation iPhones and Tegra devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Xposed Framework</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-xposed-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 14:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-install-xposed-framework/</guid>
      <description>Xposed is a popular framework that allows you to modify and customize your Android device without having to flash a new rom. It allows you to use a variety of apps and tools (such as gravity box) that extend what you can achieve with your Android device. If you&amp;#8217;re tinkerer or someone who thrives on complete control, than Xposed it what you want. For more techinical details on Xposed read this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Boost Speaker Volume</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-boost-speaker-volume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 04:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-boost-speaker-volume/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s face it. Even at max volume, sometimes the speaker on your phone just isn&amp;#8217;t loud enough (Yes, I&amp;#8217;m looking at you Nexus 5). However, you could digitally raise the maximum volume that the speaker allows itself to go to. This will require a rooted android device and could run the risk of damaging your speakers if you go too high, so be warned.
What You will Need:  A rooted Android Device ES File Explorer  Step 1: Mounting the System Open up ES file explorer and enable the root explorer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Play Nintendo DS Games on Android</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-nintendo-ds-games-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 15:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-play-nintendo-ds-games-on-android/</guid>
      <description>The Nintendo DS was by far one of my favorite portable game systems. However, these were the days before smartphone gaming became the norm. If you&amp;#8217;re feeling nostalgic and in the mood to play some DS games on your Android device, it&amp;#8217;s very easy thanks to the DraStic DS emulator. Here&amp;#8217;s how to play Nintendo DS games on Android:
What You&amp;#8217;ll Need:  A Nintendo Game (nds Rom)(You can Google it) DraStic DS Emulator (Demo) DraStic DS Emulator (Full)  Step 1: Transferring the Rom to Your Device The first thing you need to do is transfer the Rom to your device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Floating Window</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-floating-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 04:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/android-floating-window/</guid>
      <description>One of the most iconic features of the Galaxy Note 3, is the multi-window feature. It&amp;#8217;s extremely cool and makes great use of the abundance of screen real estate. Unfortunately, that&amp;#8217;s not a native Android feature. However, with the help of an Xposed Module, you can achieve the floating affect on any android device. Here&amp;#8217;s how to get Android floating window display:
What You Will Need:  A rooted Android Device Xposed Installer App Halo App(Android 4.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>