<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>phone on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/phone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in phone on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 03:02:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/phone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Pixel Phone Disappointment</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/google-pixel-phone-disappointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 03:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/google-pixel-phone-disappointment/</guid>
      <description>Google has announced their new phone, the Pixel. It&amp;#8217;s coming off the heels of the forever loved Nexus program. IMO, this new Google Phone is asking too much while offering too little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oneplus 3 Review</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/oneplus-3-review-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 14:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/oneplus-3-review-2/</guid>
      <description>After using the Oneplus for a week, I want to share my opinion of the device. Mainly focusing on the things that I really liked about it and the things that I didn&amp;#8217;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oneplus 3 Review</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/oneplus-3-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 14:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/oneplus-3-review/</guid>
      <description>After using the Oneplus for a week, I want to share my opinion of the device. Mainly focusing on the things that I really liked about it and the things that I didn&amp;#8217;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s on my Phone</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/whats-on-my-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 14:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/whats-on-my-phone/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;#8217;s on my phone? I want to share with you some of the Android apps that I use on my phone everyday.
Android Customization:  Nova Launcher Iride UI is Hipster Zooper Widget Zooper Widget Theme  Productivity:  Google Keep Todoist Inbox Evernote Calendar Widget  Texting:  Textra  Social:  Buffer Fenix Sync for Reddit  &amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Phone From Android Wear</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-phone-from-android-wear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 14:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lock-phone-from-android-wear/</guid>
      <description>Security means everything to me. I am that guy who uses two step authentication on everything, along with safety backups and more. When it comes to security on Android, things aren&amp;#8217;t as tight as I would like them to be. On my S6, my favorite thing to use is the fingerprint scanner. I am aware that the fingerprint scanner does not offer better security than a strong password or lock pattern (although you could easily bypass the Android Lockscreen pattern), however, it will deter most people from trying to snoop around in my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LG G4 Quick Review</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-quick-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 02:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/lg-g4-quick-review/</guid>
      <description>tl;dr
The LG G4 is seriously one of the best Android smartphones of 2015. It might not have the most attractive design on the outside and in the UI, but it is very responsive and can last you through a whole day with moderate-heavy usage.
The LG G4 Quick Review: Here is a quick review of the LG G4.
Screen: The LG G4 has a 2560x1440p display. LG calls it a quantum HD display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Root Any Android Device</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-root-any-android-device-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/how-to-root-any-android-device-2014/</guid>
      <description>There are some things in life that sound too good to be true. However, this isn&amp;#8217;t one of them. George Hortz, a hacker made famous by his iOS jailbreaks and PlayStation hacks has managed to root the Verizon Galaxy S5. So why should you care? Well, he used a recently discovered exploit found in all Linux kernels that were built prior to June 3rd. So in theory (and in practice) his app should work on any Android device that has a kernel build date prior to June 3rd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/share-computer-internet-connection-with-android-reverse-tethering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 23:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/share-computer-internet-connection-with-android-reverse-tethering/</guid>
      <description>Everyone is familiar with tethering. However, many people overlook the ability to reverse tether. Reverse tethering allows you to share your computer&amp;#8217;s internet connection with your phone or tablet. This is useful if you&amp;#8217;re on a metered data plan or in an area which has no wifi and a weak mobile signal. 
What You Will Need:  A rooted Android Device A Windows PC USB Driver Reverse Tether Zip (Go to this thread to download or direct download here)  Step 1: Install USB Drivers If you don&amp;#8217;t have any device drivers already installed on your computer and you never used adb before, then you will need to install the USB drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>