<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stream on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://bennettnotes.com/tags/stream/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stream on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 13:31:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bennettnotes.com/tags/stream/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Games to Chromebook using Moonlight</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/stream-games-to-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 13:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/stream-games-to-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>If you want to play Fortnite or PUBG on a Chromebook, you can do this through streaming. It&amp;#8217;s very easy to stream games to Chromebook using Moonlight. The only requirement is that you need to have an NVidia 600 Series or higher graphics card.
Enable Streaming in GeForce Experience App The first thing you need to do is enable streaming in the GeForce Experience app.
Install Moonlight Extension on Chromebook You can go here to download the moonlight extension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Steam Games to Android 2017</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-android-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 02:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-android-2017/</guid>
      <description>If all Android phones came with DirectX and desktop graphics, then playing native games would be a breeze. Unfortautnetly, that is far from the case. So while you might not be able to play Fallout 4 on android, there is nothing stopping you from streaming it to your device. Here&amp;#8217;s how you can Stream Steams Games to Android.
What You Will Need:  Nvidia 600 series or better graphics Card GeForce Experience App Moonlight  If your graphics card doesn&amp;#8217;t fit the requirements, then check out my other tutorial on how to Stream Steam Games to Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Steam Games Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 15:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Hopefully it is clear by now that Chromebooks are not meant for gaming of any type. However, that hasn&amp;#8217;t stopped many of you from accomplishing things like playing CS:GO on your Chromebook or PS2 Games. However, games like CS:GO and TF2 will work on almost any piece of hardware, but something like Fallout 4 won&amp;#8217;t.
[adinserter block=&amp;#8221;5&amp;#8243;]
If you&amp;#8217;re still determined to game from your Chromebook, you can do so via streaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stream Steam Games to Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-to-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 13:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/stream-steam-games-to-android/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to play Team Fortress or PlanetSide 2 on your Android device? Well, there is no way to do that, unless you&amp;#8217;re looking to play Team Fortress Classic on your Android device. However, you could stream these games from your computer to your Android device.
[adinserter block=&amp;#8221;5&amp;#8243;]
Currently, the most popular method used to stream games to Android is some combination of limelight and Nvidia&amp;#8217;s Game Stream.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>