<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bluetooth on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://bennettnotes.com/tags/bluetooth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bluetooth on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 15:59:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bennettnotes.com/tags/bluetooth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Android as Microphone</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/use-android-as-microphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 15:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/use-android-as-microphone/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever needed a microphone, but did not have one available? Have you ever searched for a way to make a cheap wireless microphone? Needless to say, you can use your Android device as a microphone. There are two ways that this can be accomplished. The first is through traditional cables, and the second is through additional software. If you want to use your Android device as a microphone through USB, Wifi or Bluetooth, then skip to the second method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Phone From Android Wear</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/lock-phone-from-android-wear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 14:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/lock-phone-from-android-wear/</guid>
      <description>Security means everything to me. I am that guy who uses two step authentication on everything, along with safety backups and more. When it comes to security on Android, things aren&amp;#8217;t as tight as I would like them to be. On my S6, my favorite thing to use is the fingerprint scanner. I am aware that the fingerprint scanner does not offer better security than a strong password or lock pattern (although you could easily bypass the Android Lockscreen pattern), however, it will deter most people from trying to snoop around in my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>