<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apps on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://bennettnotes.com/tags/apps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apps on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 15:28:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bennettnotes.com/tags/apps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Linux Apps</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/top-linux-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 15:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/top-linux-apps/</guid>
      <description>I spent a couple of months using Linux as my secondary operating system. During that time, I came across some really useful Linux apps that satisfied my needs. So here&amp;#8217;s my list of the top Linux Apps.
HTOP To view the running tasks in Linux, all you need to do is open up a terminal window and type in the command top. This will give you a quick running view of all the active processes on your system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Android Apps March 2017</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/top-7-android-apps-march-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 22:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/top-7-android-apps-march-2017/</guid>
      <description>Here is my pick for top 7 Android apps for March 2017.
Energy Bar No this is not a snack. This app will display your battery level as a small line above your status bar. You can adjust the thickness and position of the line. At first it&amp;#8217;s kinda distracting to look at, however, I&amp;#8217;m quickly getting used it; I just love how subtle it is. I also think it&amp;#8217;s easier to estimate my battery using this rather than looking at the battery icon in the status bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Android Holiday Apps</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/top-android-holiday-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 15:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/top-android-holiday-apps/</guid>
      <description>   Weather Timeline Reuters TV (Sponsored) Circle Sidebar Google Photoscan  GeoQpons Krazy Coupon Lady Dingless </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Extensions for Google Chrome</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/best-extensions-google-chrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/best-extensions-google-chrome/</guid>
      <description>The best thing about Google Chrome is all the extensions that are available for it. Now I recently learned that Microsoft Edge also has extensions, but nowhere near as many as google chrome. By no means is this an exhaustive list of all the best extensions for Google Chrome; just a few of my favorites that I use every day.
Ghostery 
If you are concerned about your privacy on the internet, then Ghostery is the perfect app for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Samsung Galaxy Apps</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/top-samsung-galaxy-android-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 14:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/top-samsung-galaxy-android-apps/</guid>
      <description>Here is my pick for some of the most useful Samsung Galaxy apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s on my Phone</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/whats-on-my-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 14:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/whats-on-my-phone/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;#8217;s on my phone? I want to share with you some of the Android apps that I use on my phone everyday.
Android Customization:  Nova Launcher Iride UI is Hipster Zooper Widget Zooper Widget Theme  Productivity:  Google Keep Todoist Inbox Evernote Calendar Widget  Texting:  Textra  Social:  Buffer Fenix Sync for Reddit  &amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack Android Apps and Games</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/hack-android-apps-and-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 14:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/hack-android-apps-and-games/</guid>
      <description>Wouldn&amp;#8217;t it be great if every game had cheat codes? Well, this might be closer than you think. Using the app Game Guardian, we can change the value of any numerical data within Android games. Yes, you can now achieve an unbeatable high score in your favorite game.
To do this you will need to have a rooted Android device. The process for this is fairly simple. We need to find the location of the desired attribute then change its value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy S7 RAM Management</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s7-ram-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 15:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/galaxy-s7-ram-management/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;#8217;s a look at the Galaxy S7 RAM Management. Has Samsung improved over the S6&amp;#8217;s terribly aggressive memory management?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coolest Apps Android wear 2015</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/coolest-apps-android-wear-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 14:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/coolest-apps-android-wear-2015/</guid>
      <description>I love trying out new things with my smartwatch. Here is a video featuring the coolest Android wear apps 2015. If apps aren&amp;#8217;t your thing, no problem. Check out my video on the Top Android wear games for your device.
PixToCam  Video for Android Wear Wear Audio recorder Web Browser for Android wear Staylit Wear Have any other cool apps? Feel free to share below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Android apps on Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/run-android-apps-on-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 22:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/run-android-apps-on-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>Recently, Google has released an Android run-time for Chrome OS that will allow developers to easily port their android applications to Chrome OS (Feel free to watch the Keynote for more information). While this is a step in the right direction (and should have been included with Chrome OS from the very beginning, but I digress) there are only four official android apps available for Chrome OS (Evernote, Vine, Sight Words, Duolingo).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>