<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tether on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://bennettnotes.com/tags/tether/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tether on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 14:37:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bennettnotes.com/tags/tether/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Share WiFi Connection on Android</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-share-wifi-connection-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 14:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/how-to-share-wifi-connection-on-android/</guid>
      <description>Last summer, I was staying at a beautiful resort in the Dominican Republic with no access to mobile data, so I needed to depend on WiFi. Unfortunately, my network access only allowed me to have one device at a time on the network. This was a huge pain because I wanted to connect both my phone and laptop to the network. After some searching, I found out a simple way to share wifi from an android device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/android-reverse-tether/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 19:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/android-reverse-tether/</guid>
      <description>There might come a time when you need to access the internet from your phone, but you don&amp;#8217;t have access to WiFi or mobile data. When that happens, Android Reverse Tether would be a useful thing to know. Reverse tethering means to share your computer internet connection with your phone (rather than the other way around). There are a couple of ways that you can do it. One way is to create a WiFi hotspot from your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/reverse-tether/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 13:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/reverse-tether/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube ueM2yAPGKBk {}
Have you ever been stuck in a situation that you needed WiFi but only had an Ethernet connection available? Unless you&amp;#8217;re looking to connect your phone to an Ethernet connection, you would be all out of options. I found myself in a similar situation when I needed to setup a live stream using a bunch of laptops and only one Ethernet connection with no WiFi available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Reverse Tether</title>
      <link>https://bennettnotes.com/share-computer-internet-connection-with-android-reverse-tethering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 23:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://bennettnotes.com/share-computer-internet-connection-with-android-reverse-tethering/</guid>
      <description>{{ youtube _pmoYJrTgnM {}
Everyone is familiar with tethering. However, many people overlook the ability to reverse tether. Reverse tethering allows you to share your computer&amp;#8217;s internet connection with your phone or tablet. This is useful if you&amp;#8217;re on a metered data plan or in an area which has no wifi and a weak mobile signal. 
What You Will Need:  A rooted Android Device A Windows PC USB Driver Reverse Tether Zip (Go to this thread to download or direct download here)  Step 1: Install USB Drivers If you don&amp;#8217;t have any device drivers already installed on your computer and you never used adb before, then you will need to install the USB drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>