<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Side Projects on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/side-projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Side Projects on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 05:46:53 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/tags/side-projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flying a Drone With Javascript</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/flying-a-drone-with-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 05:46:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/flying-a-drone-with-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Flying a drone with javascript probably sounds crazy and hard. Do I use a framework? Will the 10 GB of node_modules weigh it down? NOPE! It&amp;rsquo;s all pretty simple to do.
The other day I came across a neat drone called the DJI Tello. It is a relatively inexpensive quadcopter that offers a simple SDK which can be accessed over WiFI. Using the NodeJS dgram library, I can send commands via UDP to the drone to perform actions such as takeoff, left 20, and land.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success from Things You Don&#39;t Care About</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/what-you-want-vs-what-sells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 05:57:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/what-you-want-vs-what-sells/</guid>
      <description>I had just finished a YouTube that I spent a week working on; a couple of days working on the graphics, a day of voice recording, and a few more hours coming up with a nice thumbnail. I uploaded it, and eagerly awaited the YouTube algorithm to award my quality work with a burst of views and watch time. I sat and waited in anticipation. Hour one went by, nothing. Okay, maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just a little slow today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Too Absorbed in Your Side Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/getting-too-absorbed-into-your-side-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 07:01:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/getting-too-absorbed-into-your-side-projects/</guid>
      <description>When I start working on a side project, I fall into a really bad habit of getting too absorbed in it. The second I get home from work, I will start coding and testing for hours until I have to force myself to go to bed with only six hours of sleep at best. All the while, my laundry starts to pile up, my kitchen doesn&amp;rsquo;t get cleaned, and my social contacts get neglected from any meaningful conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>