<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on Bennett Notes</title>
    <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on Bennett Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 06:03:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bennettnotes.com/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I want to do everything so I do nothing</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/i-want-to-do-everything-so-i-do-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 06:03:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/i-want-to-do-everything-so-i-do-nothing/</guid>
      <description>One of the most challenging areas of self discipline in life is time management. I often find myself in situations where I do not have enough time to complete all the things that I want to do. And it&amp;rsquo;s not because I am procrastinating; the second I get home from work I jump right into some new side project or video. The problem is that there are simply too many things that I want to do right now, and learning the personal discipline to say no to myself is challenging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complacency After College</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/complacency-after-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 06:00:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/complacency-after-college/</guid>
      <description>Up until graduation day, everything made sense. I&amp;rsquo;ll go to class, get good grades, then land a decent paying job so that I can move out of my parents and &amp;ldquo;start my life&amp;rdquo;. Amazingly, all of that happened fresh out of college at 22 years old. Back then, a couple of my peers have told me, &amp;ldquo;Damn dude, you&amp;rsquo;re living the dream.&amp;rdquo; In reality, I felt like I was far from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Too Absorbed in Your Side Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/getting-too-absorbed-into-your-side-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 07:01:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/getting-too-absorbed-into-your-side-projects/</guid>
      <description>When I start working on a side project, I fall into a really bad habit of getting too absorbed in it. The second I get home from work, I will start coding and testing for hours until I have to force myself to go to bed with only six hours of sleep at best. All the while, my laundry starts to pile up, my kitchen doesn&amp;rsquo;t get cleaned, and my social contacts get neglected from any meaningful conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness and Anticipation</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/happiness-and-anticipation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 12:46:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/happiness-and-anticipation/</guid>
      <description>I am beginning to see the relationship between happiness, anticipation and dopamine.
Dopamine is a neurotransmitter that is responsible for reward-driven behavior and pleasure seeking. (Psychology Today). When we get a hit of dopamine, we feel good!
Anticipation is the simple act of looking forward; usually to a pleasurable experience but it could also be negative.
In my previous post about Proven Ways to be Happy Again, I mentioned this thing called hedonic adaptation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientifically Proven Ways to Be Happy Again</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/scientifically-proven-ways-to-be-happy-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 06:02:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/scientifically-proven-ways-to-be-happy-again/</guid>
      <description>During the winter holidays (peek depression season), I took a free online course called The Science of Well-Being offered by Yale University. It was actually recommended in a HackerNews comment that I came across in a thread about different MOOC (Massive Online Open Courses) to take.
Other than my obsession with self help porn, I took this course because I wanted to learn on how to be happy again with life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ebooks are not social</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/ebooks-are-not-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 18:26:46 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/post/ebooks-are-not-social/</guid>
      <description>If you are trying to be more social, consider investing in traditional books over EBooks. I know this sounds crazy, and no, Amazon did not pay me to say this.
Ebooks are missing an important aspect that we have always took for granted in traditional book. There is no easily visible cover! This means people have no idea on what you&amp;rsquo;re reading. With traditional books, its out in the open for everyone to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Computer Science Degree Was Not Worth the Cost</title>
      <link>https://www.bennettnotes.com/my-computer-science-degree-was-not-worth-the-cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 13:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>dave@bennettnotes.com (Dave Bennett)</author>
      <guid>https://www.bennettnotes.com/my-computer-science-degree-was-not-worth-the-cost/</guid>
      <description>I am a 2018 college graduate with a bachelor&amp;#8217;s degree in computer science. I recently got hired for my first full-time software developer job. As any new graduate, I was eager to go to work and put this shiny new degree to good use. After just a few weeks on the job, I had a horrible realization. Four years of undergrad and \$80K taught me nothing of value for today&amp;#8217;s job market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>